<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130030000 +0000" stop="20250130033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Assassin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Crittendon interferes as Hogan tries to help a defecting scientist, whom they were ordered to kill.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130033000 +0000" stop="20250130040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Cupid Comes To Stalag 13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan helps Klink fall in love with General Burkhalter's sister to get his mind off not being promoted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130040000 +0000" stop="20250130043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Tim Conway And The Pointer Sisters</sub-title>
    <desc>In Stella Toddler, Carol plays an accident-prone woman on a game show "Up Your Income". Then, in Nora Desmond, Carol plays a has-been actress who searches for a replacement for her butler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130043000 +0000" stop="20250130053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fancy Figures</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Martin Ellis is sent to jail for stealing the sum of $300,000. Ellis is later exonerated thanks to evidence discovered by his wife and the real thief, Charles Brewster, is arrested for the theft. Brewster manages to get out of jail on bail but later turns up dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130053500 +0000" stop="20250130060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Hocus-pocus And Frisby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>A loud-mouthed braggart's boasts attract the attention of aliens.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130060500 +0000" stop="20250130063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Bull In A China Shop</sub-title>
    <desc>"A handsome homicide detective is befriended by four old ladies who invite him for tea and proceed to play out a variation of Arsenic and Old Lace for his benefit."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130063500 +0000" stop="20250130070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Disappearing Trick</sub-title>
    <desc>"Walter Richmond is a gullible tennis player with a nose for snooping. He meets a woman named Laura Gild and tries to learn everything about her. His curiosity does not pay off when she and her supposedly dead husband scam him for money."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130070500 +0000" stop="20250130080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Death In The Fifth Gear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>While convalescing in a clinic after a bad car accident, Mannix helps a patient whom a doctor wants to blame for murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130080500 +0000" stop="20250130090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Deadly Heritage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Publisher Quigley asks Cannon for help. He believes that hotel proprietor Rawdon has killed six girls. When the seventh victim is found, however, it's Quigley himself who becomes the prime suspect. A lab assistant manipulates the samples used in the framework of the murders.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130090500 +0000" stop="20250130100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Killer Without A Name</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E17</episode-num>
    <desc>While on a cruise, Betty falls for a man who's being targeted by South American street police.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130100000 +0000" stop="20250130103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narco - Missing Hype</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>This episode focuses on drugs, paying particular attention to addiction symptoms.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130103000 +0000" stop="20250130110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Helpful Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Police track down a thief who specializes in elderly people.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130110000 +0000" stop="20250130113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 124 -- Airport</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are rendered powerless when a drunken man with no flight experience decides to take a solo flight in a stolen airplane at a busy airport. Later, they try to locate a 17-year-old runaway living in a condemned home with a much older man, engage in a shootout with a convenience store robber and search for a booby-trapped bank safe that has been stolen with a tow truck.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130113000 +0000" stop="20250130120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 94 -- Vengeance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy fears that a boxer who has just been paroled after serving a murder sentence is going to seek revenge against him. Out on patrol, they try to save a man who has been crushed while working under a stolen car, apprehend a liquor store robber who swears revenge against reed, change a flat tire on their patrol car, locate a four-year-old child who locked himself in a refrigerator and become the targets of an ambush.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130120000 +0000" stop="20250130130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Throwback Thursday: 1962</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony boogie through 1962!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130130000 +0000" stop="20250130133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Cleaning Up Beaver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally begins to outgrow his "sloppy" phase and becomes much neater. This is noticed by Ward and June who try to encourage Beaver to undergo the same transformation. However, Beaver changing like that just seems too extraordinary of a task.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130133000 +0000" stop="20250130140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Perfect Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward becomes a bit jealous when Wally and Beaver begin spending time playing basketball at Willie Dennison's house after Willie's dad put up a backboard and a basket. This prompts Ward to do the same thing but it just seems like things are working against him in his quest to be the perfect father.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130140000 +0000" stop="20250130150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Glamorous Ghost</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Eleanor Corbin pleads amnesia after police find her running and screaming through woods near her apartment building. Her loss of memory is of little help to her when she is later charged with murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130150000 +0000" stop="20250130160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Foursome  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock reluctantly agrees to defend millionaire Ellis Blake when he's accused of murdering his daughter's fiancé, Jeffrey Holden, a blackmailing golf caddy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130160000 +0000" stop="20250130170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Pilot: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Virgil Tibbs returns to Sparta and joins the police force as chief of detectives. His arrival is met with resistance from police chief Bill Gillespie - who resents having an officer hired without his approval. Virgil has trouble adjusting to the small, antiquated police force. Tibbs' first case is a racially charged murder case that is soon complicated when the suspect is murdered in his cell.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130170000 +0000" stop="20250130180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Hot Rod</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Jim-Bob and Jody open an auto repair place</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130180000 +0000" stop="20250130190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Foundling</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E18</episode-num>
    <desc>When the parents of a daughter who was raped refuse to accept the girl's baby, Marshal Dillon must find a home for the child.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130190000 +0000" stop="20250130200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Hound Dog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E25</episode-num>
    <desc>When Muley shows up with a pack of hound dogs, Hoss decides to train them to hunt the coyotes that have been preying on the Ponderosa livestock. However, it isn't long before the dogs' real owner shows up, saying they were stolen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130200000 +0000" stop="20250130203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Score Is Even</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas looks for help when he is shot after witnessing a murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130203000 +0000" stop="20250130210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Mescalaro Curse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is marked for death: he was foreman of a jury that convicted an Apache.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130210000 +0000" stop="20250130220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Orly French Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>"A Bible-quoting marshal joins the wagon train with his prisoner, a young bank robber whom he claims to be trying to reform. He wants the prisoner to atone for his sins by telling the location of the money he hid from his last holdup."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130220000 +0000" stop="20250130230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Pressure 165</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>John gets ribbed about his cooking. The paramedics go to Catalina to help a diver, where John and a doctor treat the patient in a hyperbaric chamber. Roy and John help a famous chef with a kitchen fire. A youth suffers a serious gunshot wound. The firemen deal with a dust explosion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130230000 +0000" stop="20250130233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>War Co-respondent</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E23</episode-num>
    <desc>B.J. finds himself attracted to a famous war correspondent, Aggie O'Shea, who has fallen in love with him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250130233000 +0000" stop="20250131000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Back Pay</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Angered by the way civilian doctors in the States are profiting from the war, Hawkeye presents the Army with a bill for his medical services. Meanwhile, Charles reluctantly demonstrates American medical practices to three Korean medics, and is on the receiving end of their medical expertise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131000000 +0000" stop="20250131003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Best Of Enemies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E01</episode-num>
    <desc>On his way to some R&amp;R in Tokyo, a North Korean soldier forces Hawkeye to perform an emergency roadside operation on his buddy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131003000 +0000" stop="20250131010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Letters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Members of the 4077th share their impressions of war in response to letters from fourth graders in Hawkeye's hometown. Margaret writes about how there are some patients she will never forget, while the Colonel tells of his days as "Hoops."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131010000 +0000" stop="20250131013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Farmer Takes A Wife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Jeff Pruitt, a farmer from the hills, comes to Mayberry in search of a wife. He enlists Barney and Andy's help and ends up picking Thelma Lou!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131013000 +0000" stop="20250131020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Keeper Of The Flame</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie joins a secret club that meets in Jubal Foster's barn. When Jubal burns his own barn down, he attempts to blame the group of boys.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131020000 +0000" stop="20250131023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed Rescues Pearl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Pearl's efforts to snag Mr. Brewster seem doomed until he makes a ridiculous public proposal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131023000 +0000" stop="20250131030000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer Makes The Honor Guard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A reluctant Sgt. Carter may be forced to use Gomer as an honor guard, as he's one of the few who owns a dress-blue uniform.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131030000 +0000" stop="20250131033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Flame Grows Higher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>When a POW is caught at the processing location after Stalag 13, Hogan suspects there is a traitor in the underground. Newkirk and LeBeau help him find out who it is.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131033000 +0000" stop="20250131040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Request Permission To Escape</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>After receiving a "Dear John" letter, Carter asks Hogan if he can escape and get back to his girlfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131040000 +0000" stop="20250131043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Family, The / Wishing Well, The</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Family, Eunice takes care of her injured and demanding friend. Then, in The Wishing Well, Harvey makes a wish and won't tell Carol what it is.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131043000 +0000" stop="20250131053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Perjured Parrot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The courtroom action in this episode takes place at a coroner's inquest as a parrot holds the key to freeing suspect Ellen Sabin from blame in the murder of her husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131053500 +0000" stop="20250131060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Trade-ins</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly couple visits the New Life Corporation, hoping to transport their personalities into youthful artificial bodies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131060500 +0000" stop="20250131063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Revenge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Revenge fuels a husband looking for the man who raped his wife</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131063500 +0000" stop="20250131070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Fatal Figures</sub-title>
    <desc>"A bookkeeper decides to come out of anonymity by committing a crime."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131070500 +0000" stop="20250131080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Open Web</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix lends a hand to a police lieutenant who's pursuing an escaped mobster into the Santa Monica mountains.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131080500 +0000" stop="20250131090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>He Who Digs A Grave (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"A serial murder targets Cannon as his next victim. At first the homicide wanted to be finally released from his compulsion to kill. Cannon accepted to help him. But Cannon got too involved in the killer's demands."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131090500 +0000" stop="20250131100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Death Is The Punchline</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A comic is suspected of killing the nightclub owner who fired him after his act proved to be a flop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131100000 +0000" stop="20250131103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Who Killed Who?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A shooting case exemplifies how the police gather—and why they must sometimes withhold—evidence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131103000 +0000" stop="20250131110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - The Son</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday investigates a woman's claim that her husband is an armed robber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131110000 +0000" stop="20250131113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 104 -- The Bomb</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed search for a suspect who frames an employee of a manufacturing plant for theft and then plants a powerful bomb on the premises. They also apprehend two criminals after questioning a suspicious man who is carrying heavy bags down the street, and protect an innocent motorist from a street race that still ends in tragedy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131113000 +0000" stop="20250131120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 74 -- Light Duty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed spend a night shift on desk duty after Malloy breaks his wrist and another office worker calls in sick. With the assistance of a new female recruit, they deal with a homesick elderly woman who refuses to identify herself, help a lenient father bail out his son and become suspicious of a man who walks in looking for a wanted fugitive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131120000 +0000" stop="20250131130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Back To '85</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony time travel back to 1985 to collect some cool stuff."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131130000 +0000" stop="20250131133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver And Poncho</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver makes a trade with Larry Mondello, a glass doorknob for a chihuahua. Larry had found the dog in his garbage can, so when Beaver brings it home, Ward immediately breaks the news that he's going to place an ad in the lost-and-found and that Beaver probably won't be able to keep the dog. Despite this, Beaver quickly begins to grow close to the little dog.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131133000 +0000" stop="20250131140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The State Vs. Beaver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward helps Beaver and Wally build a miniature race car powered by the lawn mower motor, and Ward makes the boys promise not to use it without his supervision. Later, Larry talks Beaver into taking it for a spin, resulting in the boys being pulled over by a traffic officer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131140000 +0000" stop="20250131150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Poison Pen-pal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A casual pen pal relationship leads to insider information and murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131150000 +0000" stop="20250131160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Clown  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock agrees to defend aging clown Homer Fleming after he's charged with the murder of his long-time partner. After asking Conrad to go undercover as a roustabout at the circus, Matlock learns that the deceased had many enemies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131160000 +0000" stop="20250131170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Pilot: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The investigation into the brutal murders of a young girl and the suspect in her death, leads Tibbs and Gillespie to the son of one of Sparta's wealthiest and most influential citizens. As they come closer to the truth things become dangerous for Virgil.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131170000 +0000" stop="20250131180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Gold Watch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Stanley Perkins is retired and returns to the mountain to see Rose</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131180000 +0000" stop="20250131190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Iron Blood Of Courage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Gunfighter William Talley is hired by a farmer's coalition in Dodge to kill rancher Shaw Anderson, their main obstacle in taking over land they want.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131190000 +0000" stop="20250131200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Trap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E26</episode-num>
    <desc>When her husband is murdered, Hallie Shannon is convinced that her former sweetheart, Joe Cartwright, committed the deed so they could be together again.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131200000 +0000" stop="20250131203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Stopover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Trouble brews at Lucas' when a whisky salesman and a gunfighter fall for the same woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131203000 +0000" stop="20250131210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Lonesome Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Two pranksters write away for a mail-order bride, using Lucas's name.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131210000 +0000" stop="20250131220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Donna Fuller Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>"A woman and three companions in a runaway wagon are rescued by a winemaker and Charlie. They are against the consumption of alcohol and join the wagon train. However, she begins to fall for the winemaker until she learns his trade."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131220000 +0000" stop="20250131230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>One Of Those Days</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly woman's stomach problems lead to a family brawl. Roy and John treat a drunk in a hotel with a broken elevator. Doctors treat a boy with meningitis. Paramedics respond to a two-car accident with no victims, treat a man who fell in the bathtub and rescue a child trapped in a burning building.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131230000 +0000" stop="20250131233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Cementing Relationships</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A jilted Italian soldier, Corpsman Ignazio De Simone, is smitten by Margaret; Klinger pours a cement floor in the operating room to fight the spread of germs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250131233000 +0000" stop="20250201000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Father's Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret has trouble pretending she's a chip off the old block when her dad, blood and guts "Howitzer" Al Houlihan, arrives for a visit. Also, Hawkeye fixes up a soldier who repays them with a large side of steak, but the general who it belongs to is really steamed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201000000 +0000" stop="20250201003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Your Retention Please</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger is so depressed by news that his ex-wife plans to remarry, he reenlists for an additional six-year stretch. Meanwhile, a male nurse has a gripe against the Army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201003000 +0000" stop="20250201010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Tell It To The Marines</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Winchester takes command during Potter's absence; and B.J. and Hawkeye try to convince the Marines to grant a hardship discharge to an immigrant soldier, Private Jost Van Liter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201010000 +0000" stop="20250201013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Bailey's Bad Boy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Rich kid Ronald Bailey is jailed when he blatantly defies the law. As Bailey waits for his influential father to bail him out, Andy teaches him the lesson of self-responsibility.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201013000 +0000" stop="20250201020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Manicurist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A beautiful manicurist from the city comes to Floyd's to set up shop. She makes all the wives in town extremely nervous as she manicures their husbands.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201020000 +0000" stop="20250201023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Back To Californy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed is confronted with too many cooks and not enough vittles when he invites Pearl and Jethrine to Beverly Hills.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201023000 +0000" stop="20250201030000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>My Buddy, The War Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer tries to prevent Sgt. Carter and his long-time friend from becoming enemies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201030000 +0000" stop="20250201033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan Gives A Birthday Party</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan hijacks a German bomber, and plans to use it to destroy an oil refinery and foil a German general who knows about the his operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201033000 +0000" stop="20250201040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Schultz Brigade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink and two other prison camp kommandants are arrested for conspiring against General Burkhalter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201040000 +0000" stop="20250201043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Roddy Mcdowall</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Family, Mama and family visit Hollywood to see her son. Then, in The Lady Heir, the gang parodies the classic film "The Heiress", with Carol as Olivia de Havilland and Roddy as Montgomery Clift.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201043000 +0000" stop="20250201053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Shattered Dream</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Sarah Werner asks Mason to find her husband, Hugo Werner, who ran off with her inheritance. Hugo, now using the name Hans Breel, is working on a gem scam but his scheme backfires when he is murdered and Sarah is charged with the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201053500 +0000" stop="20250201060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Gift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E32</episode-num>
    <desc>An alien crash-lands in a remote mountain village, stirring up fear and animosity among the villagers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201060500 +0000" stop="20250201063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Death Sentence</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>When a woman finds a bomb in her car, it convinces her that her husband loves her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201063500 +0000" stop="20250201070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Listen, Listen</sub-title>
    <desc>"Three women have been strangled. Police arrest a stocking salesman as the killer. Mr. Morgan knows who the real culprit is: he has seen the next murder in a dream. He tries to tell people, but no one listens. His wife ignores him as well, which is unfortunate because she is the strangler's next victim."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201070500 +0000" stop="20250201080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Question Of Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A young boy asks Mannix to prove that his hero did not die from a hit-and-run accident but rather was murdered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201080500 +0000" stop="20250201090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>He Who Digs A Grave: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A lady journalist is forced to reveal her sources in a murder news or she will go to jail on a contempt charge. She enlist Cannon's service to unravel the murder of a missing excursionist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201090500 +0000" stop="20250201100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Final Victim, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A columnist writing about prostitution focuses on a murdered girl whose reputation Barnaby is trying to save.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201100000 +0000" stop="20250201103000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Valley Has A Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The pregnant Betty Jo is ready to have her baby, but problems arise when Wendell, the conductor, won't wake up and Betty Jo has to drive the train herself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201103000 +0000" stop="20250201110000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Granny, The Baby Expert</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Betty Jo and baby return from the hospital for a stay at the Shady Rest, where they are to be looked after by Dr. Granny Clampett, a kooky distant relative whose nearsightedness finds her mistaking Dog for the baby.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201110000 +0000" stop="20250201113000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Granny Tonics A Birdwatcher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E31</episode-num>
    <desc>It is Tonic Time, and Granny has made a small batch, which is enough for the family and a few friends. She also hopes that she can tonic a man for Elly May to marry. Though Elly may not have a husband in her future, Jane thinks she does. She thinks that Professor Biddle will propose to her, but he reveals all he wants her to do is hatch a condor egg. Granny heads to the bank to get Jane and Drysdale to give Dash Riprock some of her tonic.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201113000 +0000" stop="20250201120000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Courtship Of Homer Noodleman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts leave Hooterville after spending Thanksgiving there. They return to their mansion, telling Drysdale and Jane about the boy Elly started dating. When Drysdale hears of this, he decides to get a country boy to come and court Elly. He employs Dash Riprock to play country boy Homer Noodleman. After the Clampetts are introduced to Homer, Granny wants to meet his father.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201120000 +0000" stop="20250201123000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>A Jolly Good Furlough, Learn Polikeness, Popeye Makes A Movie</sub-title>
    <desc>"Popeye's four little nephews welcome him back from the war zone with a home front defense drill that nearly wrecks him., Olive tries to make a gentleman out of Popeye by taking him to Bluto's school of etiquette., Popeye and Olive make a movie for his nephews."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201123000 +0000" stop="20250201130000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Bowling Alley Cat, Little Tinker, Sufferin' Cats</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tom and Jerry are at the bowling alley as mayhem ensues., A young skunk is looking for a girlfriend but his odor is too much for most females to handle., Jerry is a prize to be won between Tom and an alley cat because neither feline wants to share him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201130000 +0000" stop="20250201140000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Screwdriver, Meatless Tuesday, Davey Cricket, Get Lost, Maw And Paw, Polar Pests, Barber Of Seville</sub-title>
    <desc>"Woody is driving erratically and a slow-witted policeman tries to apprehend him., Andy unsuccessfully tries to roast Charlie Chicken for his meatless Tuesday dinner., Charlie tries unsuccessfully to silence a crickett in his house., Woody's niece and nephew find themselves in a Hansel and Gretal situation with a hungry cat., Milford, the family pig, wins a new car for the family, but no one knows how to drive it., Chilly tries to avoid becoming a replacement penguin at the zoo., Woody goes for a haircut. When he sees the barber isn't in, he attempts to cut his own hair and that of the other clients."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201140000 +0000" stop="20250201150000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Knights Must Fall, Lovelorn Leghorn, Hare Tonic, Scent-imental Over You, Daffy Flies North, Knight-mare Hare</sub-title>
    <desc>"In medieval times, for the horrendous act of tossing a half- eaten carrot into a suit of armor, Bugs Bunny is challenged to a duel by Sir Pantsalot of Drop Seat Manor. , Foggy is being attacked by the dog, but turns the situation into a football match. , Elmer Fudd takes Bugs home for his "wabbit stew"., On Park Avenue and 86th Street, all the fancy dogs except a little female Mexican hairless are sporting new coats. , Daffy needs to go south, but he doesn't want to fly. Instead he tries to find alternate means of getting there. , An apple falls on Bugs' hairdryer sending him back to medieval England."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201150000 +0000" stop="20250201160000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Wolf</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Assigned to protect Stefan, who is to be crowned king in place of his late brother, the agents must deal with the sinister Mr. Talamantes. Talamantes wants Stefan to renounce the throne and will do anything to accomplish this goal. This includes kidnapping Stefan's daughter, Leandra, and manipulating her to do his bidding whenever she hears or reads a certain word.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201160000 +0000" stop="20250201170000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Sam Darland Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>"The wagon train finds Sam Darland with orphan boys in an old ghost town. Hale tries to convince Darland that it is not safe to stay in the town, as it in the midst of Indian territory and the leader of the tribe has been on the warpath."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201170000 +0000" stop="20250201180000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>A Time To Kill</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Jarrod welcomes an old law school friend to the valley, only to find that a secret service agent is on his trail. It seems that every place the friend travels, counterfeit money comes into circulation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201180000 +0000" stop="20250201190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Schoolmarm</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E20</episode-num>
    <desc>After being raped, Dodge City school teacher Sarah Merkle struggles with the implications of being an unwed mother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201190000 +0000" stop="20250201200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Dead And Gone</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Singer Hoyt Axton guest stars as drifter Howard Mead, whose singing skills are matched only by his predilection for running afoul of the law. While trying to straighten Mead out, Adam Cartwright is forced to defend his new friend against a robbery charge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201200000 +0000" stop="20250201203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Death Trap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas recognizes Dr. Simon Battle as an ex-gunslinger with whom he once traded shots.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201203000 +0000" stop="20250201210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Queue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E34</episode-num>
    <desc>A Chinese man and his son fight prejudice as they try to open a laundry in North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201210000 +0000" stop="20250201220000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident At Farragut Pass</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>In return for letting the herd cross her land to get to water, E.J. Farragut wants Favor to hire a woman's grandson, Billy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201220000 +0000" stop="20250201223000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>The Prophet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>The Army asks Paladin to find an Army colonel who disappeared with his Apache wife. There are rumors of an Army officer working with the Apaches and inciting them to war. Paladin is asked to find and stop him at all costs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201223000 +0000" stop="20250201230000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Rope Law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh and Brace Logan are met on the range by a group of men who want Logan, Josh's prisoner. When the men take Logan by force, Josh goes to town to file a complaint. He's surprised to find the sheriff was the leader of the men. Josh is now determined to find the truth about the situation before Logan is lynched.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250201230000 +0000" stop="20250202010000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Punch Drunks, Horses' Collars, From Nurse To Worse, All The World's A Stooge, Cactus Makes Perfect, I Can Hardly Wait</sub-title>
    <desc>"Moe is a boxing promoter looking for a good fighter.  , The Stooges are private detectives in the old West trying to help a girl recover an IOU from a bad guy.   , The Stooges are defense workers who have trouble getting to sleep when Curly gets a toothache.  Moe and Larry try various ways to remove the offending tooth, but nothing works so they take Curly to the dentist.  While Moe gets in the chair to show Curly how easy it's going to be, the dentist enters and pulls Moe's tooth by mistake.  Curly then wakes up and realizes its all been a dream and a punch to the mouth from Moe dislodges the tooth. , The stooge's friend Jerry convinces them to take out on insurance on Curly and then have him act insane to collect.  Moe and Larry put Curly on a leash and take him to the insurance doctor and have him act like a dog.  Unfortunately, the insurance doctor wants to perform a brain operation (Cerebrum decapitation).  The boys try to escape by hiding in the dog catchers wagon, but are caught and taken to the hospital.  They escape again, this time by rigging a sheet to a gurney and sailing down the street, where they run into Jerry and knock him into wet cement. , The Stooges are window washers who lose their jobs after Moe impersonates the dentist in whose office they were cleaning.  On the run, they are hired by a millionaire to pose as children.  It seems the man's wife wants to adopt some refugees to impress her society friends.  Moe is Johnny, Curly is Frankie and Larry is Mabel.  Everything goes fairly well as the lady shows off the Stooges to her friends, but they finally irritate her husband so much that he goes after them with an ax. , The Stooges are living with their mother who persuades them its time to leave home and seek their fortune.  After a con man sells them a phony deed to a lost gold mine, the boys head west to find the treasure.  After some mishaps with Curly's gold finding invention, they locate the mine and strike it rich.  When two crooked miners try to take their gold they hole up in an abandoned hotel and, although they get bombarded by dynamite, triumph over the crooks. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202010000 +0000" stop="20250202033000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>20 Million Miles To Earth</sub-title>
    <desc>"The first human expedition to Venus returns to Earth in a crash landing off the coast of Italy. The only survivor is Hopper and he's frightened that he may have lost a canister holding specimens of Venusian life. 20 million miles to Earth is Ray Harryhausen's signature special effects story of a terrifying monster from Venus running wild and wreaking havoc in Italy."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202033000 +0000" stop="20250202040000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>The Duo Defy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E60</episode-num>
    <desc>Mr. Freeze obtains the instant ice formula and builds an Ice-Ray to freeze the entire country! To prove his word, he ices down various parts of Gotham.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202040000 +0000" stop="20250202050000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>Plato's Stepchildren</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Kirk and his crew find themselves at the mercy of powerful individuals who possess mind-over-matter powers and plan to use the Enterprise crew for their twisted entertainment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202050000 +0000" stop="20250202060000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>Bad Medicine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The first based on a Native American legend, a Diablero shaman spirit murders for jewels to pay back his debt and be released from his Earthly bonds.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202060000 +0000" stop="20250202070000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>Space Destructors</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Smith and the robot are exploring a cave. Smith pushes several buttons on a conspicuous control panel. The buttons activate a cyborg-creating device. It is up to Will to stop Dr. Smith.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202070000 +0000" stop="20250202080000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Creature</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Seaview searches the ocean floor for the force that caused an aborted missile launch."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202080000 +0000" stop="20250202090000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>The Crash</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The Spindrift is drawn through a space warp and crashes on a planet where everything is twelve times larger than Earth. They must quickly learn to deal with a hostile environment while becoming the target of giant scientists who want to capture and study them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202090000 +0000" stop="20250202100000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>The Revenge Of Robin Hood</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>In 13th-century England, Tony and Doug join Robin Hood's revolt against evil King John.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202100000 +0000" stop="20250202110000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Life Seekers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A police shooting causes Vincent to investigate a possible alien encounter with hidden secrets.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202110000 +0000" stop="20250202120000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>Endurance (aka Survival)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Asylum escapees endanger Matt's classmates as they travel to an outdoor survival course."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202120000 +0000" stop="20250202123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Graduation   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>On graduation day, Zack discovers that he is one credit short of getting his diploma, and the only way he can earn it is by doing the unbelievable—BALLET!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202123000 +0000" stop="20250202130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Time Capsule   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Mr. Belding and the class of 2003 find a video time capsule from the class of 1993. The video shows the funny and the touching moments Zack and the gang shared with each other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202130000 +0000" stop="20250202133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>King Of The Hill   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack starts high school ready to woo longtime crush Kelly, but A.C. Slater stands in his way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202133000 +0000" stop="20250202140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Fatal Distraction   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After Zack spies on Kelly, trying to hear who'll she'll take to the dance, she sets up a prank to get even.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202140000 +0000" stop="20250202143000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Screech's Woman   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Trying to cheer Screech up so he'll complete their science project, Zack pretends to know a girl who is interested in him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202143000 +0000" stop="20250202150000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Gift   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After a freak accident, Screech can predict the future, an ability Zack uses to his advantage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202150000 +0000" stop="20250202153000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Today, I Am A Freshman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>It's the beginning of another school year, and Marcia panics about becoming a freshman, going as far as pretending to be sick. However, after Mike and Carol see through her act, they insist she'd enjoy school if she were involved in extracurricular activities. Marcia then proceeds to join every group or club available. Meanwhile, Peter tries to build a model volcano on the patio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202153000 +0000" stop="20250202160000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Fright Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The boys trick Jan and Cindy into thinking they've seen a ghost. The girls plot their revenge, but it's Alice, Carol and Mike who mistakenly end up as their victims.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202160000 +0000" stop="20250202163000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Nose For News</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>After getting a "D" on a paper for his investigative reporting class, Richie decides to do a story about the corrupt sanitation department, which is forcing Howard to pay a weekly surcharge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202163000 +0000" stop="20250202170000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Lost In Spacesuits</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Desperate for money, Laverne is offered a job at Ajax Aerospace by one of Frank's old Army buddies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202170000 +0000" stop="20250202173000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Jinx</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>After a series of mishaps, Henry Bennett gets a reputation in town as a jinx. The more Andy tries to dispel the rumor the deeper the hole gets, until Henry decides it would be best if he left town altogether.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202173000 +0000" stop="20250202180000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Lucy Goes To The Hospital</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Ricky and the Mertzes rehearse for pregnant Lucy's trip to the hospital. It turns out to be predictably chaotic, but Lucy does deliver Little Ricky.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202180000 +0000" stop="20250202183000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Broken Window</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>While playing baseball in the street with Wally, Chester and Tooey, Eddie hits a baseball through the Cleaver's window resulting in Ward forbidding the boys to play baseball so close to the house. However, later, Beaver talks Wally into pitching one, and this results in a broken car window.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202183000 +0000" stop="20250202190000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Train Trip</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>After a week-long visit with their Aunt Martha, Wally and Beaver prepare to head home to Mayfield on a train. After talking Martha into letting them buy their own tickets, they discover they're short the money after spending it on junk food and find themselves wondering how they are going to get home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202190000 +0000" stop="20250202193000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Party Line</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny and Jethro return to Elly and Jed after visiting Pearl back home. Granny returns with presents and a new device, a telephone. For Granny, this phone is high tech. She gets Jethro to install it, but he installs wrong, connecting wires to a light pole instead of a telephone pole, electrocuting himself, causing it to blow up and making Granny go temporarily deaf.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202193000 +0000" stop="20250202200000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Soup Contest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny enters Elly in a soup-making contest, with her own Snider Surprise soup. When Jed finds out Granny cheated, he demands that she pull Elly May out of the contest. But Granny refuses to because this is a way to get Elly a husband. She tricks Jed into believing she got Elly out of the contest and gets him to go hunting, just in time. The men from Savory Soup visit the mansion and are amazed by the beautiful Elly, thinking she’d be a beetle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202200000 +0000" stop="20250202203000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>It's A Bird, It's A Plane</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A U.S. Air Force jetpack washes ashore in the lagoon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202203000 +0000" stop="20250202210000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>The Pigeon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E28</episode-num>
    <desc>The Professor sees the arrival of a homing pigeon on the island as an opportunity to be rescued.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202210000 +0000" stop="20250202213000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Best Policy  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After Naomi takes out a large life insurance policy on Vint, Mama and Iola think Naomi is trying to kill Vint for insurance money when he suffers a series of household accidents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202213000 +0000" stop="20250202220000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>After The Fall  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After Aunt Effie falls off the roof, she is stuck in a trance-like state.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202220000 +0000" stop="20250202230000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Good Time Girls / Iron Man / Soap Star</sub-title>
    <desc>Three college women are mistaken for prostitutes; a fitness expert suffers fainting spells during triathlon training; a soap-opera star's jealous friend "auditions" for a new part with the lecherous costar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202230000 +0000" stop="20250202233000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Jailbreak</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>State police come to town in search of payroll robbers. They want Andy and Barney to stay out of the way, but end up needing them more than they thought.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250202233000 +0000" stop="20250203000000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Tv Costumes- Henry Truglio</sub-title>
    <desc>"As a child, some of Henry's favorite memories are sitting together with his family and watching their favorite TV shows from the 70's and 80's. As an adult, he decided it would be cool to own costumes from some of the shows he loved best. These days, Henry is a well known collector of TV costumes and props, so having Lisa Whelchel in his home and being able to show her something she may have worn on Facts of Life, which is coincidentally, one of Henry's alltime favorite shows,  was definitely a "pinch me" moment for our collector. A Laverne &amp; Shirley skirt, a Peg Bundy top and a Carol Burnett dress are just a few of the iconic TV costumes Henry's managed to get his hands on. You might recognize our expert Stewart, as one of our collectors' from last season and someone with his own impressive collection of TV costumes and props.Stewart appraises Henry's collection and brings along one of his special costumes in the hopes that Henry will want to make a trade."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203000000 +0000" stop="20250203003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Taking The Fifth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye uses a bottle of vintage wine to lure unsuspecting nurses into his den; and Potter tries to secure a different sort of anesthetic when the army threatens to ban a painkiller.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203003000 +0000" stop="20250203010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Friendship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger saves Winchester's life when an explosion rocks the operating room; and B.J. is reluctant to reveal the extent of his injuries after the blast.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203010000 +0000" stop="20250203013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of The Waitress</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith finally confronts the waitress who tempted Archie's fidelity after Harry unwittingly hires her to work at Archie's Place.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203013000 +0000" stop="20250203020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Bogus Bills</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith is arrested for passing phony $10 bills she got from Archie's Place.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203020000 +0000" stop="20250203023000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Bunker's Go West</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E11</episode-num>
    <desc>After Mike and Gloria cancel their trip home for Christmas, the Bunkers decide to travel west for the holidays.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203023000 +0000" stop="20250203030000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>California, Here We Come (part 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The Bunkers head out to California for Christmas to find out that Mike and Gloria are having marital problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203030000 +0000" stop="20250203033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Goodbye Charlie / As The Stomach Turns</sub-title>
    <desc>In Goodbye Charlie, Tim writes a eulogy for his best friend, only to discover he was wooing his wife. Then, in As the Stomach Turns, Carol's daughter comes back to life as a Bionic Woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203033000 +0000" stop="20250203040000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Steve Lawrence And Sally Struthers</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Boring Twenties, Carol and the gang parody the classic film "The Roaring Twenties", following a singer in a dumpy bar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203040000 +0000" stop="20250203043000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Lady And The Babysitter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Richie's teenage babysitter has a crush on Laura.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203043000 +0000" stop="20250203050000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Vigilante Ripped My Sports Coat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Crabgrass leads to crabby neighbors as Rob and Jerry start a feud.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203050000 +0000" stop="20250203053000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Loudspeaker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph writes a speech because he thinks he's going to be Raccoon of the Year—but it turns out Norton receives the honor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203053000 +0000" stop="20250203060000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Dummy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A ventriloquist is convinced that his dummy is not only alive but also evil.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203060000 +0000" stop="20250203070000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Hangover  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A man wakes up with a hangover, an unknown woman in his room and his wife lost.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203070000 +0000" stop="20250203080000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Falcon: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney manages to make his way to the vault despite his blindness and replace the real jewels with fakes. Paris disguised as Nicolai slips Francesca a gun and she fake-shoots herself at the altar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203080000 +0000" stop="20250203090000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Smoke Screen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A forest fire prevents access to a local hospital. Kimble, now a farm laborer, decides to risk blowing his cover when he elects to help deliver a woman's baby at the labor camp. When the news of Kimble's charitable act is reported to the press, Gerard get</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203090000 +0000" stop="20250203100000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Coinage Of The Realm</sub-title>
    <desc>"The carnival atmosphere of an amusement park adds a bizarre twist to Harry O's attempt to save a little girl's life and prevent a gangland murder."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203100000 +0000" stop="20250203103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>A.i.d. - The Weekend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon confront a phony magazine salesperson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203103000 +0000" stop="20250203110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narco - Pill Maker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>It's a job half done when police nab a narcotics manufacturer: they still need his backer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203110000 +0000" stop="20250203113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 114 -- The Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed witness a young hispanic man save a trapped watchman from a burning warehouse, but become suspicious when he resists numerous attempts of private and public commendation. They also try to prevent a drunken man from falling out a window, and resuscitate a man with a heart condition.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203113000 +0000" stop="20250203120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 134 -- Child Stealer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed has to deal with the consequences of forgetting to roll up the window on the patrol car before he left it. Back on patrol, Malloy and Reed search for an estranged husband who kidnaps his own child, deal with an elderly man who tries to pay for a meal with trading stamps, engage in a shootout with an escaped prisoner caught napping on a city bus and pull over a hijacked delivery van full of booze.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203120000 +0000" stop="20250203130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Inspiring Women In Black History</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony pay tribute to trailblazing African American women."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203130000 +0000" stop="20250203133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Next Door Indians</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Wanting to be liked by Wally's friends, Beaver makes up a wild story about the vacant lot next to his house being an Indian battle ground. After making a bet with Eddie, Beaver has Wally help him plant artifacts in the lot. However, that is forgotten when the kids make a discovery that they believe will make them rich.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203133000 +0000" stop="20250203140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Tenting Tonight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>After a weekend spent at the movies goes awry for Ward, he decides the boys should spend their weekends outside and plans a camping trip. However, when Ward's called into work, Wally and Beaver decide to camp out in the backyard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203140000 +0000" stop="20250203150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Mystified Miner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason tries to clear his young, beautiful client after a twisting and wheeling plot of murder, kidnapping and embezzlement unfolds.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203150000 +0000" stop="20250203160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Prisoner: Part 1  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a prison guard is accused of murder, Matlock goes into the prison to defend him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203160000 +0000" stop="20250203170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Road Kill</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The affair between the husband of a wealthy woman and her distant cousin leads to her murder. Virgil immediately suspects the pair. But he has a difficult time persuading Gillespie, who is a longtime friend of the man and Bubba, who has been seeing the cousin. Bubba and Virgil clash again and Virgil is frustrated when the Chief rejects his theory about the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203170000 +0000" stop="20250203180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Beginning</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Another new minister begins at Walton's Mountain. The church is in disarray, but he gets the community involved.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203180000 +0000" stop="20250203190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Trail Of Bloodshed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Buck Henry Woolf is on the trail of his uncle, who killed his father, stole their money and wounded him. Festus is on the same mission and also to stop the young man from taking the law into his own hands.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203190000 +0000" stop="20250203200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Good Night's Rest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben's noisy sons are keeping him from sleeping, prompting a trip to the hotel in town. But rather than finding sanctuary, Ben is bothered by more noise and other irritations that prevent him from a good night's rest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203200000 +0000" stop="20250203203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Vaqueros</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>While Lucas and Mark are traveling across the Mexican desert they encounter a trio of Mexican bandits. They demand payment from Lucas for crossing "their" desert. Lucas refuses. In retaliation, the three slam Lucas in the throat with his rifle, strip him of all his possessions (including Mark), tie him to a tree and leave him to die of thirst and exposure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203203000 +0000" stop="20250203210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>First Wages</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas tries to find out why Mark has taken a job as a stableboy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203210000 +0000" stop="20250203220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Abel Weatherly Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>"A sea captain traveling west haunted by nightmares from his past is found stranded, injured and drunk by Bill and Charlie. After hearing his story, they help him reach his destination to locate a ghost: a dead sailor that may be alive."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203220000 +0000" stop="20250203230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Lighter-than-air Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>En route to a rescue, Roy and John supposedly sideswipe an elderly crossing guard. A couple on their way to a wedding hits a fire hydrant. A burning camper drives up to the station house. A truck carrying insecticide overturns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203230000 +0000" stop="20250203233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>No Sweat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret develops a case of prickly heat, Charles does his tax returns and Klinger takes the P.A. apart—just some of the events that occur during another unendurably hot night at the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250203233000 +0000" stop="20250204000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Depressing News</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger's army newspaper reports on Hawkeye's monument to military stupidity; a giant tower made from a half million erroneously shipped tongue depressors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204000000 +0000" stop="20250204003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>No Laughing Matter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye wagers that he can go a full day without a wisecrack, and Winchester finally confronts the major who exiled him to the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204003000 +0000" stop="20250204010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Oh, How We Danced</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Winchester is sent to inspect sanitary conditions on the frontlines, while the rest of the camp plans a surprise anniversary party for B.J.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204010000 +0000" stop="20250204013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Medal For Opie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie has his heart set on winning a medal in a foot race at the town picnic. When he loses, he exhibits poor sportmanship. Andy teaches him a lesson about being a good sport.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204013000 +0000" stop="20250204020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney And The Choir</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When the awful sound coming from the Mayberry choir is narrowed down to Barney, the members decide they must get rid of him, but no one has the heart to do it. They devise a plan with an allegedly super-sensitive microphone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204020000 +0000" stop="20250204023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed's Dilemma</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Pearl is trying to give Granny a break, figuring that Granny is so old and feeble that she cannot perform her household chores anymore. This upsets Granny greatly because she knows she can still get the job done. Granny chases after Pearl, and Jed decides to get the family to relax by taking them sightseeing around Beverly Hills.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204023000 +0000" stop="20250204030000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Cannon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The mobile state museum is brought to Mayberry for Founder's Day. Goober and Warren stand guard and end up firing the old Civil War cannon at two burglars.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204030000 +0000" stop="20250204033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Diamonds In The Rough</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A German officer threatens to expose Hogan unless he is paid a million dollars in diamonds.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204033000 +0000" stop="20250204040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Briefcase</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is ordered to give a German general a briefcase containing a time bomb to assassinate Hitler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204040000 +0000" stop="20250204043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Jean Stapleton And Phil Silvers</sub-title>
    <desc>In Tacky Lady, Carol sings dressed as Cher. Then, in TV Commercials, Carol and the gang parody TV products, including Boritos Corn Chips, Zerts, Moe DiMaggio, Meannen After Shave Lotion, Drop-off, Bruce Hancock, Kleenies, Nite-O-Quill, Coffee, and Irregularity. Next, in The Old Folks, Carol thinks Harvey forgot their anniversary. Finally, in Hallway Encounter, a woman-libber holds her ground against her complaining boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204043000 +0000" stop="20250204053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Borrowed Brunette</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Eva Martell is hired out of numerous candidates by Melvin Slater to impersonate a woman named Helen Reynolds. Eva is paid extremely well and given a nice apartment for assuming the identity of Helen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204053500 +0000" stop="20250204060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Young Man's Fancy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E34</episode-num>
    <desc>When a newlywed couple visit the groom's childhood home, the ties of the past prove too strong to resist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204060500 +0000" stop="20250204063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Post Mortem</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman learns that a winning sweepstakes ticket is in the suit her husband was buried in.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204063500 +0000" stop="20250204070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Crocodile Case</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E34</episode-num>
    <desc>A man murders his lover's husband to have her for himself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204070500 +0000" stop="20250204080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Trap For A Pigeon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is hired to find a stolen briefcase containing bribery money in a mob murder case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204080500 +0000" stop="20250204090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Memo From A Dead Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A rich lady, Cecilia Lasher, hires Cannon to locate the son her husband abandoned years before. She turns to Cannon after being blackmailed and terrorized.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204090500 +0000" stop="20250204100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Silent Accuser, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Betty responds to an SOS from her teacher friend, only to find her dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204100000 +0000" stop="20250204103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - The Dognappers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon set out to muzzle thieves who steal dogs and then collect hefty rewards from the owners.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204103000 +0000" stop="20250204110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Missing Persons - The Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Working with the slimmest of leads, police attempt to identify a woman's body.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204110000 +0000" stop="20250204113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 144 -- Bank Robbery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are in for a rude awakening when they report to the home of a former professional wrestler on a domestic abuse call. Later, they become suspicious of an apartment burglary victim after they find one of the suspects dead, deal with a man who discovers car parts that were stolen from him installed on another car and become involved in a shootout responding to a bank robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204113000 +0000" stop="20250204120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 44 -- Attempted Bribery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A wealthy businessman openly offers malloy and reed security jobs at three times their current salaries if reed agrees to withhold damaging testimony against his troubled son. In the meantime, they have to deal with an elderly man who has strangled his ch</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204120000 +0000" stop="20250204130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>*5 Star Critic</sub-title>
    <desc>"Toony aspires to become a food critic with a little help from Bill!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204130000 +0000" stop="20250204133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Music Lesson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally makes the baseball team and Ward openly shows how proud he is of him, leaving Beaver feeling inferior. Trying to impress his parents, Beaver tries out for the band and begins practicing the clarinet. However, Beaver soon finds himself with more problems when he's let go from the band.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204133000 +0000" stop="20250204140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>New Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>June has Wally stay home from school when he comes down with a sore throat and suddenly Wally is immersed in attention from his parents, friends and doctor. Jealous and feeling left out, Beaver fakes illness, seeking that same attention.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204140000 +0000" stop="20250204150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Crippled Cougar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike Preston is a bitter man who despises Hugh Jamison because he mistakenly believes Jamison stole $100,000 from him and is responsible for him being crippled. Trying to entrap Jamison, Preston makes a mistake and is set up for murder by the real culprit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204150000 +0000" stop="20250204160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Prisoner: Part 2  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a prison guard is accused of murder, Matlock goes into the prison to defend him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204160000 +0000" stop="20250204170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Fate</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Racial tensions run high when a married white woman has an affair with a black businessman from New York. Meanwhile Virgil is not happy when the Chief enlists his aid in tracking down Bubba's cousin, a suspected moonshiner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204170000 +0000" stop="20250204180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Pearls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Corabeth returns to her family home to help a dying aunt</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204180000 +0000" stop="20250204190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Cowtown Hustler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A broke young man seeks his fortune with an old drifter, a formerly legendary champion billiards player.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204190000 +0000" stop="20250204200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>To Own The World</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E29</episode-num>
    <desc>A rich tycoon known for destroying anything that stands in his way vows to have the Ponderosa, no matter the cost.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204200000 +0000" stop="20250204203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Sheer Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark and Milly are held prisoner in her general store when two gunmen attempt a daring robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204203000 +0000" stop="20250204210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Stand-in</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Two prison wagon drivers stop at the McCain ranch looking for whiskey. Lucas turns them down because they are escorting Rudy Croft, a murderer who is to be hanged in Yuma.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204210000 +0000" stop="20250204220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Davey Baxter Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>"When his wagon falls down a cliff, Davey Baxter's mother is killed, and his arm is crushed. The doctor is unavailable, so Chris is forced to make the decision to amputate. This changes everything for Davey and the girl he plans to marry."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204220000 +0000" stop="20250204230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Simple Adjustment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Swamped with paperwork, the paramedics are continually distracted by emergencies: a girl trapped in an overturned car, a beautician who has taken too many diet pills, an elderly man and workers stuck on a blazing ship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204230000 +0000" stop="20250204233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bottoms Up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E15</episode-num>
    <desc>One of Margaret's nurses tries to hide her severe drinking problem, and Hawkeye is scorned after a practical joke he plays on Winchester backfires.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250204233000 +0000" stop="20250205000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Red/white Blues</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Potter nearly blows his stack when his well-intentioned colleagues mollycoddle him in order to lower his blood pressure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250205000000 +0000" stop="20250205003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bless You, Hawkeye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E17</episode-num>
    <desc>When Hawkeye can't stop a sneezing fit that has no apparent cause, psychiatrist Sidney Freedman digs into the surgeon's past for a clue to this unusual malady.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250205003000 +0000" stop="20250205010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Blood Brothers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye is overcome by the devotion of a terminally ill G.I., who has leukemia, for his critically wounded buddy, but he has trouble coming to terms with the fact that he can't cure the man. Meanwhile, Father Mulcahy is worried about the impending visit of a Cardinal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250205010000 +0000" stop="20250205013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Of Honor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>As a sort of publicity stunt, the town decides to pull over the first car that drives through Mayberry and make its occupant the town's guest of honor. That lucky driver? A recently released convict.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250205013000 +0000" stop="20250205020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Merchant Of Mayberry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Traveling salesman Bert Miller is getting tired of traveling, so Andy and Barney plan to help him set up a small general goods shop on a vacant lot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250205020000 +0000" stop="20250205023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed Saves Drysdale's Marriage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>When Pearl calls to yodel for him as a surprise, Jane suggests to Drysdale that he employs Pearl to be the head housekeeper, and when he suggests it to Pearl, she thinks he means marriage. And when Granny and Jed visit Mrs. Drysdale, who is going to a health spa, she says how Milburn is getting a more glamorous wife in her, but they think Drysdale is getting a brand new wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250205023000 +0000" stop="20250205030000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>The Jet Set</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer accidentally takes a wrong turn on his way downtown and winds up on a round-trip jet flight to Rome.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250205030000 +0000" stop="20250205033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Battle Of Stalag 13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Two German officers interfere with Hogan's operations when one tries to turn Stalag 13 into an officer's retirement home the other wants to use the facilities to interrogate the citizens of the local town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250205033000 +0000" stop="20250205040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Rise And Fall Of Sergeant Schultz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is stymied in the rescue of a captured member of the underground until a potential diversion appears in the form of an old WWI buddy of Sgt. Schultz.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250205040000 +0000" stop="20250205043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Family, Eunice and Mama stop by her husband's hardware store, only to get in another fight. Then, in Shower Blackout, Carol steps out of the shower singing "When Your Lover Has Gone". Finally, in The Oldest Man, Harvey gets his grandfather clock fixed by the Oldest Man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250205043000 +0000" stop="20250205053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Glittering Goldfish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>An inventor of a cure for sick fish is charged with the murder of the purchaser of a pet fish store.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250205053500 +0000" stop="20250205060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>I Sing The Body Electric</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E35</episode-num>
    <desc>A widower buys a robotic grandmother for his three children.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250205060500 +0000" stop="20250205063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Premonition</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A pianist returns to his home town, hoping to mend a broken relationship with his father, and instead finds mystery and foreboding in everything he encounters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250205063500 +0000" stop="20250205070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Safe Place</sub-title>
    <desc>"A bank teller schemes the perfect plan."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250205070500 +0000" stop="20250205080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Ragged Edge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix goes undercover as a heroin addict to discover who's trying to kill an old friend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250205080500 +0000" stop="20250205090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Hounds Of Hell</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank travels to a small ranching town to help out a writer friend charged with a double murder. Frank's only clue is a cryptic note left by the man's wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250205090500 +0000" stop="20250205100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Deadline For Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A pair of men pretending to be Barnaby and J.R. murder a writer employed by a publishing empire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250205100000 +0000" stop="20250205103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Forgery - The Ranger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Other people's credit cards are found in the possession of a forest ranger.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
