<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240907180000 +0000" stop="20240907190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Burma Rarity</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Widow Hawkins tricks a couple of con men who first try to swindle her with an emerald known as "The Burma Rarity."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240907190000 +0000" stop="20240907200000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident At Spider Rock</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A hot time on the old town nets the drovers assorted bruises, and a spirited girl bent on making the cowhands pay for wrecking her saloon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240907200000 +0000" stop="20240907203000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Homecoming</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Wrongly convicted Ed Stacy, whom Paladin helped to put in prison, is being released after being pardoned. Will Stanhope, who runs the local freight office, hires Paladin to protect him from Stacy. Paladin soon wonders who is really in danger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240907203000 +0000" stop="20240907210000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>The Long Search</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Yoshika Nakamura comes west to find a man named Bill Timmons, who promised to marry her when he visited Japan. Yoshika hires Josh to help her locate Timmons, and during his venture learns about Japanese culture.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240907210000 +0000" stop="20240907213000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadly Wait</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Maury, released from Yuma prison, arrives in North Fork intent on getting even with Marshal Torrance, who helped send him to jail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240907213000 +0000" stop="20240907220000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Wrong Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Young Mark McCain is eager to help lawman Jay Jefferson, who has arrived in North Fork intent on killing an outlaw for the reward, whether he is the right man or not.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240907220000 +0000" stop="20240908000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>All Gummed Up, Love At First Bite, Bedlam In Paradise, Blunder Boys, Crime On Their Hands, I'm A Monkey's Uncle</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges run a drug store and are about to have their lease taken away by the Flint, the mean old man who owns the place.  When Flint kicks his wife out for being old, the Stooges try to help her by inventing a formula that makes old people young.  Their concoction turns the wife into a beautiful young woman, and Flint offers the boys the store for free if they'll transform him as well.  They agree, but after he swallows the stuff he turns into an infant, and the boys leave on the run.
, The Stooges reminisce about the girls they met overseas while in the military.  As they wait for the girls' ship to arrive, they get drunk and Shemp winds up asleep with his feet in a tub of cement.  After sobering up, they free Shemp with a dynamite blast that lands them at the dock where their sweethearts are waiting.
, Set in the stone age, the stooges are cavemen who must have various misadventures hunting, gathering, and otherwise coping with prehistoric life. 
, Shemp dies but cannot get into heaven until he reforms Moe and Larry.  He returns to earth as an invisible spirit and sets out to prevent the other two Stooges, who are in league with the devil, from selling a phony invention (a fountain pen that writes under whip cream) to a rich couple.  Shemp sabotages Moe and Larry' plans and makes it through the pearly gates.
, A parody of the television series Dragnet.
, The Stooges are janitors working in a newspaper office.  When an anonymous caller phones in a tip about the theft a famous diamond, the boys decide to become reporters and go after the crooks.  They find the crooks, but Shemp accidentally swallows the diamond, which was hidden in a bowl of candy.  The crooks want to cut the diamond out, but the boys foil them with the help of a friendly gorilla.
"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908000000 +0000" stop="20240908023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Killer Klowns From Outer Space</sub-title>
    <desc>"One-of-a-kind alien invasion sci-fi featuring blood drinking alien clowns harvesting a small city."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908023000 +0000" stop="20240908030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>Louie's Lethal Lilac Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>When Louie the Lilac kidnaps Bruce Wayne and Dick Grayson, it's up to Batgirl and Alfred to save them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908030000 +0000" stop="20240908040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>Patterns Of Force</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The Enterprise seeks out a historical researcher with whom the Federation has lost contact, and discover he has contaminated a culture, remaking it into a near-duplicate of Nazi Germany.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908040000 +0000" stop="20240908050000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>Horror In The Heights</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A Hindu Rakshasa terrorizes a Jewish neighborhood.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908050000 +0000" stop="20240908060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Space Vikings</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A storm looms and the two gloves of Thor appear from space and fly straight into the waiting hands of Dr. Smith. They are then taken away by the real Thor, who will decide their fate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908060000 +0000" stop="20240908070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Submarine Sunk Here</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The Seaview blunders into a minefield, where an explosion cripples the vessel and sends it to the bottom of the sea.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908070000 +0000" stop="20240908080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>The Clones</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Two giant scientists capture Barry, Valerie, Fitzhugh, and Dan, and use them in a cloning experiment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908080000 +0000" stop="20240908090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Raiders From Outer Space</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Tony and Doug are at Khartoum in 1883 when the world is menaced by conquerors from outer space.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908090000 +0000" stop="20240908100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Spores</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Aliens plot to make a new resilient race.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908100000 +0000" stop="20240908110000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>Road Rebels</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt joins a gang to stop jewel thieves connected to car robberies."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908110000 +0000" stop="20240908113000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Wicked Stepbrother: Part 1   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Jessie meets her new stepbrother, Eric, soon discovering that he possesses a dark side.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908113000 +0000" stop="20240908120000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Wicked Stepbrother: Part 2   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Jessie's new stepbrother, Eric, runs afoul of the gang and even takes Mr. Belding's car apart.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908120000 +0000" stop="20240908123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Fake Ids   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Zack falls for a college girl, he lies about his age and makes fake IDs so he, Slater and Screech can sneak into an 18-and-over dance club. While there, they see Kelly's boyfriend dancing with another girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908123000 +0000" stop="20240908130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Date Auction   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The school holds a dance-date auction to pay for new cheerleading uniforms, with Zach, Slater and Screech up for auction. Jessie is appalled at the whole idea; meanwhile, Lisa becomes an intellectual to impress a smart boy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908130000 +0000" stop="20240908133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Hold Me Tight   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a girl is rejected from wrestling tryouts because she is female, Zack, who has a crush on her, will do whatever it takes to see that she makes the team.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908133000 +0000" stop="20240908140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Love Machine   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Jessie becomes alarmed at the presence of Slater's old flame, especially when Screech's "love machine" shows that both Slater and his ex still have feelings for each other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908140000 +0000" stop="20240908143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Where There's Smoke</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Greg is spotted puffing on a cigarette with some members of a rock band. Mike and Carol get word, but refrain from punishing him. However, it's not long before a pack of cigarettes falls out of his letterman jacket.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908143000 +0000" stop="20240908150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Will The Real Jan Brady Please Stand Up?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Jan is upset when her friend, Lucy Winters, sends a birthday party invitation but accidentally addresses it to Marcia. Tired of being the middle blonde girl of the family, Jan tries to alter her appearance by buying a black wig, which she intends to wear to Lucy's upcoming birthday party. Meanwhile, Peter is horrified that Margie will be attending the party, a girl who has a major crush on him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908150000 +0000" stop="20240908153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>You Get What You Pay For</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Howard hires Fonzie's students to build a second bathroom. However, when he learns that the room will take all semester to complete, Howard fires Fonzie and the students and says he'll finish the bathroom himself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908153000 +0000" stop="20240908160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Councilman Defazio</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank is making his usual contribution to his local councilman. After the guy has taken Frank's money, he tells him that he plans to tear down Cowboy Bill's and build a high-rise on top of it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908160000 +0000" stop="20240908163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Bargain Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee, in a flurry of cost-cutting measures, saves money on beef by buying a whole side of it. Unfortunately, this happens at the same time her freezer breaks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908163000 +0000" stop="20240908170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Off To Florida</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When Lucy misplaces two train tickets to Florida, she and Ethel consult the classified section, hoping to share a ride with someone driving south. They team up with a peculiar middle-aged woman, Mrs. Grundy, who's bent on getting to Florida in record time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908170000 +0000" stop="20240908173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie's Sweater</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Eddie has been seeing one particular girl, Cindy Andrews, and she wants to give Eddie a birthday gift, so she decides to knit a sweater. She uses Wally as a model and he begins spending so much time at Cindy's he arrouses the suspicions of Julie, Eddie, Lumpy, Beaver and his parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908173000 +0000" stop="20240908180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Book Report</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has been assigned to write a book report on 'The Three Musketeers.' However he's waited right down to the wire to get reading and quickly realizes that he'll never get finished. So, he decides to watch the movie that's going to be on TV and write his book report based on the movie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908180000 +0000" stop="20240908183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Granny Goes To Hooterville</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Right after the Clampett's return from London, Granny gets a letter saying she is needed in Hooterville. The problem is that nobody knows where it is. Granny tries to find out, but doesn’t have much luck. Jethro, who isn't getting fed because Granny is focusing on Hooterville, is desperate for food and accidentally eats Elly's grits and rocks for her critters. Granny has to “doctor” him back to health.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908183000 +0000" stop="20240908190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Italian Cook</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny has been staying in Petticoat Junction, and her family is hungry. Elly May decides to take over the cooking, though her dishes are worse than eating nothing. The clan asks Granny to come home, but she says she can’t. So Jane suggests to Jethro that he hire a cook, and he ends up getting a gorgeous cook that only speaks Italian.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908190000 +0000" stop="20240908193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Forward March</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>The castaways are frightened as the sounds of battle, including hand grenades and machine guns, rock the island. The culprit turns out to be a gorilla who has found in an old WWII arsenal cave.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908193000 +0000" stop="20240908200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Ship Ahoax</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The castaways begin to suffer from "island madness" due to the isolation. The Professor attempts to come up with a plan to lift everyone's spirits.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908200000 +0000" stop="20240908203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Amateur Night  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After Vint wins a talent contest, he changes his name to "Vinnie Vegas" and sets his sights on becoming an entertainer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908203000 +0000" stop="20240908210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mama Who Came To Dinner  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Naomi talks Mama into letting her use the house for a dinner party, but when Mama suffers a back spasm the occasion is jeopardized.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908210000 +0000" stop="20240908220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Musical Cabins</sub-title>
    <desc>A young bachelor must marry within the week in order to claim a $3 million inheritance; meanwhile, a drab widow poses as a glamorous adventuress and captures the heart of the captain. Also, a confirmed male chauvinist angers his fiancee, who finds comfort in sick bay with Doc. And, a scandal sheet reporter sets out to compile material for a sins-at-sea story.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908220000 +0000" stop="20240908223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Divorce, Mountain Style</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy finds himself embroiled in a strange backwoods divorce ritual, ending up as the object of Charlene Darling's affections.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908223000 +0000" stop="20240908230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Props/costumes- Wally Wingert</sub-title>
    <desc>"Voice actor and puppeteer Wally Wingert has a joyful obsession with the pop culture of the '60s through the 1980s, so much so that he's turned his Los Angeles home into what he calls "Wallywood": a virtual musem of treasures including Jack Lord's "Hawaii 5-O" ensemble (complete with height-enhancing boots), the actual passport of Ed McMahon (Wally's predecessor as "Tonight Show" announcer), the very first licensed Kermit puppet (from before he was even a frog), and the iconic stage costume of comedy legend Andy Kaufman... plus so much more! Lisa's invited "Collector's Call" favorite Rob Klein to put a value on Wally's entire collection... then to try to tempt him into a trade, an offer that comes down to a very small piece of colored resin with a very big '60s TV connection!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908230000 +0000" stop="20240908233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>To Market, To Market</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After black marketers hijack the 4077th's supply of hydrocortisone, Hawkeye and Trapper concoct a deal with local black marketer, Charlie Lee, to get some more. The catch: Henry's antique oak desk, which they must trade in order to get the medicine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240908233000 +0000" stop="20240909000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Requiem For A Lightweight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Trapper and Hawkeye seek to keep a new nurse from being transferred by Hot Lips, and they vie for her affection. Henry Blake, challenged by another commander to a boxing tournament, makes Trapper fight a big, intimidating soldier in exchange for keeping the nurse at the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909000000 +0000" stop="20240909003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith Breaks Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie feels abandoned after Edith begins to volunteer part-time at the Sunshine Home for the Elderly.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909003000 +0000" stop="20240909010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Grandpa Blues</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie has difficuly keeping his blood pressure down for a company physical after the family launches into a heavy debate over the baby's name.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909010000 +0000" stop="20240909013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Gloria Suspects Mike</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Gloria suspects hanky-panky when she meets the beautiful blonde Mike's been tutoring after school hours.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909013000 +0000" stop="20240909020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Little Atheist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Thanksgiving dinner becomes a family battleground when Archie discovers that Mike and Gloria don't want to impose the family's religious beliefs on their baby.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909020000 +0000" stop="20240909023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Mel Torme And Michele Lee</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Mel Torme and Michele Lee. Originally aired on 01/18/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909023000 +0000" stop="20240909030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Flip Wilson And Vikki Carr</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Flip Wilson and Vikki Carr. Originally aired on 01/19/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909030000 +0000" stop="20240909033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>It's A Shame She Married Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob tries to hide Laura from a big-wig she used to date and who happens to be a sponsor for "The Alan Brady Show".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909033000 +0000" stop="20240909040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Surprise Surprise Is A Surprise</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Laura tries to give Rob a surprise birthday party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909040000 +0000" stop="20240909043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Hello, Mom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>"Ralph sleeps at the Nortons' to avoid his visiting mother-in-law. 
"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909043000 +0000" stop="20240909050000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Changing Of The Guard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E37</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly private school teacher wonders if his life has meant anything as he contemplates suicide on Christmas Eve.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909050000 +0000" stop="20240909060000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>You'll Be The Death Of Me  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A bride is overwhelmed by a growing fear that her companion committed a murder—and that she may be his next victim.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909060000 +0000" stop="20240909070000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Never Wave Goodbye (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Dr. Kimble still fleeing with the woman he loves, decides to fake their deaths at sea, hoping it will fool Lieutenant Gerald forever."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909070000 +0000" stop="20240909080000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Bunker: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Erich Rojak and his wife Anna are being held in an underground laboratory/bunker by a totalitarian enemy government. Another unfriendly government has sent an assassin, Ventlos, to kill Rojak.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909080000 +0000" stop="20240909083000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Statue Of Limitations</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Mathews attempts to catch three robbers before the statute of limitations runs out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909083000 +0000" stop="20240909090000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Interrogation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A new officer has been arrested for robbing a liquor store while on an undercover assignment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909090000 +0000" stop="20240909093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Masked Bandits</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Four bandits wearing red masks commit a series of robberies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909093000 +0000" stop="20240909100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Bank Examiner Swindle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Two con men, posing as bank examiners, are bilking the elderly out of their life savings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909100000 +0000" stop="20240909103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Hammer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly apartment manager is found to have been beaten to death with a hammer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909103000 +0000" stop="20240909110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 83 -- A Different Thing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>An older husband complains about his wife and friend's noisy karate practice. A hit and run traffic accident looks looks like a homicide. The officers use their investigative skills to locate the suspect and arrest him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909110000 +0000" stop="20240909120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Teddy Bear Necessities</sub-title>
    <desc>"Happy National Teddy Bear Day from Bill, Toony, and of course, Teddy Roosevelt himself."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909120000 +0000" stop="20240909123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Poor Loser</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward is given two tickets to a baseball game and is faced with an impossible decision. Should he take Wally or Beaver? Beaver lets him off the hook when he announces he has plans with Gilbert. However, when they fall through, Beaver changes his mind about the game and becomes convinced because he's the youngest he gets the short stick.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909123000 +0000" stop="20240909130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Don Juan Beaver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E32</episode-num>
    <desc>A school dance has Beaver with a major dilemma. He has two girls who ask him to go with them. However, he has a little problem, he accepted the first invitation but now wants out of it when he's asked by the second girl. This leads him to take some of Eddie's poor advice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909130000 +0000" stop="20240909140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Corresponding Corpse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason receives a telephone call from George Beaumont, a man who supposedly died in a plane crash nearly three years earlier. In reality, Beaumont missed the plane and after hearing about the accident decided to disappear.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909140000 +0000" stop="20240909150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Doctors  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When an abhorred doctor meets his end, four of his former medical students are considered likely suspects. Matlock, however, is tasked with defending the prime suspect, the man seen fleeing the scene of the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909150000 +0000" stop="20240909160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>My Name Is Hank</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A young refugee claims to be the son of a Sparta cop who died in the war. But quickly becomes a suspect in a murder/robbery after he accepts a ride with the criminals who actually committed the crime. Gillespie looks into his story, while Virgil and the boys track down the shooter. Meanwhile, the young man’s presence triggers a surprisingly bitter reaction from Parker, who views him as a painful reminder of the war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909160000 +0000" stop="20240909170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Best Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Olivia wants this Christmas to be the best ever</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909170000 +0000" stop="20240909180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Reprisal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Doc is given the choice of saving the life of a man he saw commit a murder or delivering a baby. He choses to save the man first, and the baby dies in childbirth. The baby's father, Tom Butler, blames Doc and plans to get even.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909180000 +0000" stop="20240909190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Broken Ballad</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The situation goes from bad to worse when Adam tries to smooth things over between a general store owner and the gunfighter who killed the man's son years earlier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909190000 +0000" stop="20240909193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Challenge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>When escaped convicts hold up the general store in North Fork and take Marshal Torrance hostage, Lucas comes to the rescue.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909193000 +0000" stop="20240909200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Hawk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Young Mark manages to capture a hawk, but then falls into danger from a rattlesnake. When a stranger comes to his rescue, the grateful Mark invites the man home, unaware that he is on the run from the law.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909200000 +0000" stop="20240909210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Stagecoach Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The men are returning to St. Louis by stagecoach except for Flint, until he becomes the driver to help a friend. They are forced to take a detour through Mexico by other passengers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909210000 +0000" stop="20240909213000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Badge Heavy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed puts his reputation on the line when he decides to file a formal complaint against a fellow officer after witnessing him use excessive force. On patrol, he and Malloy search for suspects in two separate robberies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909213000 +0000" stop="20240909220000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Harry Nobody</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed's investigation of a fatal shooting in a hotel room hinges on the eyewitness account of a hopeless wino named Harry who is desperate to make a name for himself. Meanwhile, they investigate a report of a peeping tom at the home of an exotic dancer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909220000 +0000" stop="20240909223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Chief Surgeon Who?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank Burns complains about Hawkeye Pierce's disrespect, and when Henry appoints Hawkeye chief surgeon, it's to Burns' shock. The rest of the 4077th "coronates" Hawk while Frank and Hot Lips complain to General Barker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909223000 +0000" stop="20240909230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Moose</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Sergeant Baker arrives at the camp with his "moose." Hawkeye decides to find a way of getting her away from Baker. He tries ordering him to release her, tries buying her and then resorts to cheating at cards. He releases her but she won't go, so he tries to teach her how to be independent.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909230000 +0000" stop="20240909233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Yankee Doodle Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th is designated as the setting for the making of an army film on Mobile Army Surgical Hospital units. Hawkeye is chosen as the star while Margaret and Frank compose a screenplay. Hawkeye objects to the piece of propaganda that filmmaker Lt. Bricker is producing and, having exposed the original film, reshoots a new one his way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240909233000 +0000" stop="20240910000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bananas, Crackers And Nuts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When Henry goes for some R&amp;R, Hawkeye pretends to crack up so that Frank will let him and Trapper go on some R&amp;R.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910000000 +0000" stop="20240910003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Deal Is A Deal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>In their efforts to win a pony, Opie and his friends become involved in a scam that has them shilling a useless miracle salve.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910003000 +0000" stop="20240910010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Fun Girls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney are working late at the courthouse when they get a visit from two wild women. Out of pure kindness, they drive the "fun girls" home, but don't know that Helen and Thelma Lou saw them with the women.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910010000 +0000" stop="20240910013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Another Neighbor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Countess Maria comes to Beverly Hills, making Mrs. Drysdale very excited. But she wants to keep the countess away from the hillbillies. However, it's spring tonic time, and Granny passes it around the neighborhood, including at Countess Maria's house. She falls in love with the brew and visits the Clampetts. They become friends instantly. She starts falling for Jed, and has plans to marry her 6th husband, hoping it is an American.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910013000 +0000" stop="20240910020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>The Price Of Apples</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Oliver will make considerable more on his apple crop if he gets his to market first. He hires local highschoolers to pick the fruit and uses their old truck to haul them. As the rickety truck suffers numerous breakdowns, the apple prices begin to drop. Finally, Lisa's hotcakes come to the rescue.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910020000 +0000" stop="20240910023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>That's No Lady, That's My Spy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Newkirk poses as a general's wife to get penicillin to an ill underground leader.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910023000 +0000" stop="20240910030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>To Russia Without Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan arranges for a beautiful Russian spy to convince Klink that the Kommandant should volunteer for service at the Russian front. Hogan's payoff: some secret papers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910030000 +0000" stop="20240910033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Soupy Sales And Mel Torme</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Soupy Sales and Mel Torme. Originally aired on 01/26/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910033000 +0000" stop="20240910043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Bullied Bowler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After a struggling bowling alley is shut down at the insistence of a domineering townswoman, a doctor involved in the closure is found murdered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910043500 +0000" stop="20240910050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>In Praise Of Pip</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>An alcoholic bookie regrets that he wasn't a better father to his son, Pip, critically wounded in South Vietnam.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910050500 +0000" stop="20240910060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Blood Bargain  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A contract assassin reneges after meeting his target's handicapped wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910060500 +0000" stop="20240910070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Game Plan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>When the daughter of one of Mannix's friends is kidnapped, the captors demand that the man lose a large sum of money in a card game as her ransom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910070500 +0000" stop="20240910080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Murder For Murder</sub-title>
    <desc>A writer was murdered. His latest book would deal with the biography of an industrialist. Cannon must protect the co-author and investigate the activities of the industrialist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910080500 +0000" stop="20240910090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Beware The Dog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A dog is the prime suspect in the fatal mauling of a man whose stepson is the dog's owner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910090000 +0000" stop="20240910093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Resident Officer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Mathews searches for the murderers of a fellow officer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910093000 +0000" stop="20240910100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Candy Store Robberies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon try to figure out a pattern to a series of candy store hold-ups. The solution comes when they discover that there are two suspects.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910100000 +0000" stop="20240910103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Fur Job</sub-title>
    <desc>"Gannon goes undercover as a buyer in order to trap fur thieves"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910103000 +0000" stop="20240910110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 103 -- A Sound Like Thunder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and his date join Reed and his expecting wife on a weekend trip to a ghost town, but soon they cross paths with a dangerous motorcycle gang.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910110000 +0000" stop="20240910120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Bill Goes To Homecoming</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill receives a special invitation to attend the homecoming dance at his old high school."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910120000 +0000" stop="20240910123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Summer In Alaska</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Eddie is happy to break the news that he plans to spend his summer on a fishing boat in Alaska and this prompts Wally and Lumpy to think about signing up to do the same thing. However, they all get a dose of reality when they discover just what kind of conditions they would be living in.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910123000 +0000" stop="20240910130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Graduation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E34</episode-num>
    <desc>It's come down to the final week before junior high school graduation and Beaver is having a ball and even skips a class with Gilbert. However, Beaver becomes convinced he won't graduate after Gilbert and him take a peek at the diplomas on Mrs. Rayburn's desk and find Beaver's diploma to be missing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910130000 +0000" stop="20240910140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lucky Loser</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason has all kinds of trouble when a murder brings him into the tangled financial and personal affairs of the wealthy Balfour family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910140000 +0000" stop="20240910150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Billionaire: Part 1  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock flies to England to represent Eric Gordon, a man accused of murdering his wealthy businessman father. While his sister is convinced of his innocence, his brother isn't so sure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910150000 +0000" stop="20240910160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>King's Ransom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The F.B.I. tries to talk an ex-boxer into testifying against a mobster he once worked for, but the fighter sees the situation as an opportunity for blackmail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910160000 +0000" stop="20240910170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Mustang</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A wild mustang is captured on Walton land and Grandpa wants it to remain be and remain free</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910170000 +0000" stop="20240910180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Long Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Three bounty hunters hold hostages in the Long Branch in an effort to get Matt to turn over a prisoner to them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910180000 +0000" stop="20240910190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Many Faces Of Gideon Flinch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Bullethead Burke is looking for a man he says cheated him out of $5,000 dollars. The man's niece tricks Little Joe and Hoss into helping her uncle out. A pickpocket escapes from jail and complicates matters even more.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910190000 +0000" stop="20240910193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Three-legged Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>When a rambunctious teenager wrecks a schoolroom, Lucas McCain, as a member of the North Fork school board, asks the boy's reluctant uncle to pay for the damages.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910193000 +0000" stop="20240910200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Angry Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>The McCains try to be tolerant of their embittered neighbor, Abel MacDonald, who tells Lucas to keep off his land and won't allow his son to become friends with Mark. However, McCain decides he's gone too far when he won't allow his injured boy to get medical treatment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910200000 +0000" stop="20240910210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Greenhorn Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>During any wagon train trip, the challenges and losses faced turn the greenhorn into a seasoned veteran.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910210000 +0000" stop="20240910213000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Surprise</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>It's Malloy's birthday, but he's consumed with anger over the thought his colleagues might have a plan to throw him a surprise party. On a busy patrol, he and Reed make an ironic traffic stop while responding to a burglary call at an antique store, deal with an extremely embarrassed theft victim at a lingerie store, investigate suspicious activity at a service station, use a creative approach to apprehend a serial jewelry store burglar and engage in a shootout inside the police station's parking garage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910213000 +0000" stop="20240910220000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Vendetta</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed suspect that a well-armed immigrant tailor who claims to be defending his establishment from burglars is actually plotting a murder. In the meantime, they deal with a drunken traveling businessman who passes out in a bar girl's car.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910220000 +0000" stop="20240910223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Cowboy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>John Hodges, a chopper pilot referred to as The Cowboy, has been hit in the shoulder, and arrives at the 4077th. He is expecting a letter—he's worried that his wife, Jean, is leaving him for another man. He wants to go home, but Henry refuses, stating Cowboy's wound isn't serious enough to merit a stateside ticket. Bad luck then follows Henry Blake like the seat of his pants!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910223000 +0000" stop="20240910230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Henry, Please Come Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>When Col. Henry Blake is transferred to Tokyo and Frank starts imposing military discipline on the camp, the surgeons will do anything to get Henry back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910230000 +0000" stop="20240910233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>I Hate A Mystery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A rash of thefts breaks out in the camp. Missing pieces include Frank's silver picture frame, Margaret's hair brush and Trapper's watch. The camp is searched and everything is found in Hawkeye's locker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240910233000 +0000" stop="20240911000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Germ Warfare</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye moves a wounded North Korean soldier into The Swamp, rather than let him be shipped out before he's stable. During the night he and Trapper play Dracula, and siphon off a pint of Frank's blood. The soldier then contracts hepatitis, so they have to test Frank without him knowing, and have to keep him away from Margaret and the patients.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911000000 +0000" stop="20240911003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of Malcolm Merriweather</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee gets upset when Malcolm Merriweather returns to Mayberry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911003000 +0000" stop="20240911010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Rumor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E29</episode-num>
    <desc>When Barney sees Andy kissing Helen in a jewelry store, he gets the idea that they are engaged. So he starts planning an engagement party and gets the whole town involved.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911010000 +0000" stop="20240911013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>A Plot For Granny</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>For Granny’s birthday, the Clampetts plan to surprise her with some land in the country. Jed calls a number Jethro saw an ad for. However, the Clampetts do not know they are calling a cemetery. After a misunderstanding, the men from the cemetery begin believing the Clampetts are cold-blooded killers, having killed an entire family named Green, Granny and Mrs. Drysdale.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911013000 +0000" stop="20240911020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>What's In A Name?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph Monroe finds herself smitten with Hank Kimball, but discovers that he won't date a woman with a man's name. She asks Oliver to file court papers to have her name changed to something more feminine. While in court, Oliver learns that his license to practice law is not recognized by the state. This sends Oliver back to the books to study for the state's bar exam.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911020000 +0000" stop="20240911023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Klink For The Defense</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink is appointed defense counsel for a German officer on trial for treason who has secret plans intended for London. Hogan helps Klink prove the officer's innocence in order to secure the plans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911023000 +0000" stop="20240911030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Kamikazes Are Coming</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The guys find a new rocket that has landed near camp. They are at a loss on how to get it back to England for study when Marya and her rocket-designing husband enter camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911030000 +0000" stop="20240911033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Barbara Feldon And Joan Rivers</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Barbara Feldon and Joan Rivers. Originally aired on 02/02/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911033000 +0000" stop="20240911043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Shifty Shoebox</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Robbery, embezzlement and a coverup at a trucking company end in the murder of one of the owners.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911043500 +0000" stop="20240911050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Steel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Boxing robot "Battling Maxo" breaks down before a match, forcing its manager to take its place in the ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911050500 +0000" stop="20240911060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Nothing Ever Happens In Linvale  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>An eye-catching widow tries to convince an incredulous police officer that her neighbor murdered his partner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911060500 +0000" stop="20240911070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Fine Day For Dying</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>One might think that after waking from a year-long coma, the worst would be in the past. But that is not true for Mannix's client, injured in a hit-and-run accident and now the target of killers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911070500 +0000" stop="20240911080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Bobby Loved Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon delivers a ransom, but the deal goes bad and Cannon winds up with no memory of the event, kidnappers on his trail, and people willing to exploit his lack of memory.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911080500 +0000" stop="20240911090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Blood Relations</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby is hired to replace a detective who was murdered while looking for a woman's biological mother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911090000 +0000" stop="20240911093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Counterfeit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Mathews tracks down a ring of expert forgers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911093000 +0000" stop="20240911100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Jade Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>More than $200,000 worth of imperial jade is reported stolen. Friday and Gannon determine the burglary was an inside job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911100000 +0000" stop="20240911103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Shooting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A police officer is shot while making a routine check on a pair of paroled convicts parked near a liquor store.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911103000 +0000" stop="20240911110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 63 -- Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed's wife is in the hospital expecting their first child, and Reed soon regrets his decision to report for work as usual. Out on patrol, they encounter a drunken man directing traffic, chase down a robbery suspect, investigate the theft of money from washing machines and become involved in a minor traffic accident that results in a major delay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911110000 +0000" stop="20240911120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>The Peach State</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony have Georgia on ther minds."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911120000 +0000" stop="20240911123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Practical Joke</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and Eddie fall prey to Lumpy's practical joking after he plants cherry bombs under the hoods of Eddie's car and Wally's car. Both Eddie and Wally want to get him back but their plan goes awry when they destroy Lumpy's car after chaining it to a tree. All fingers point to Wally after Fred finds that the chain has Ward's name printed on it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911123000 +0000" stop="20240911130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The All-night Party</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E36</episode-num>
    <desc>After graduation, an all-night party is set to begin, which has June and Ward very wary. They aren't sure if they should allow Wally to attend. Meanwhile, Wally's date for the party has the same problem. This leads her to invite Wally to meet her folks and put their worries to rest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911130000 +0000" stop="20240911140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Pint-sized Client</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Robbers lift a bundle from the Hargrove Finance Company and Frank Anderson is murdered in the aftermath. Anthony "Pop" Renzi is identified as one of the robbers and charged with both the robbery and the murder. Mason sets out to clear him of both charges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911140000 +0000" stop="20240911150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Billionaire: Part 2  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock flies to England to represent Eric Gordon, a man accused of murdering his wealthy businessman father. While his sister is convinced of his innocence, his brother isn't so sure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911150000 +0000" stop="20240911160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Epitaph For A Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A longtime friend of the Chief makes threats against a doctor he believes is responsible for his wife's death .When the doctor is killed he becomes the prime suspect. But Gillespie doubts his guilt - even after he confesses.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911160000 +0000" stop="20240911170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Rebellion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Another woman begins to play the church organ instead of Grandma which upsets Grandma</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911170000 +0000" stop="20240911180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Riders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Kansas raider Judge Proctor and his men ride into Dodge looking for a man they blame for stealing their land during the war. With Matt out of town, Festus has to try to keep peace and keep the renegades from burning the town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911180000 +0000" stop="20240911190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Friendship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe befriends and takes responsibility for an ex-convict named Danny. Danny loves horses and is not used to people's ways on the outside of jail. Will his rough jailhouse upbringing mar any hopes of friendship?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911190000 +0000" stop="20240911193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>An unfounded rumor causes North Fork's outspoken feminist schoolteacher to be attacked by a mob of angry townspeople.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911193000 +0000" stop="20240911200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Money Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E33</episode-num>
    <desc>When his employer begins to suspect him of embezzlement, bookkeeper Asa Manning decides to hire a professional gunman to take care of the problem.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911200000 +0000" stop="20240911210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The C.l. Harding Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A reporter has joined the wagon train. When the Major finds out he is a she, he has his hands full, especially when curiosity jeopardizes everyone's safety and their right to vote.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911210000 +0000" stop="20240911213000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Chaser</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed investigate an interstate bounty hunter who has an invalid gun permit and questionable tactics. Meanwhile, they deal with an elderly man who strongly dislikes hippies, and a frustrated wife who desperately wants to receive a traffic ticket.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911213000 +0000" stop="20240911220000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Spell</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>On an unseasonably hot day, Malloy and Reed suspect that an elusive bicyclist who overreacts to having his air pump stolen in a park is actually a drug pusher. Meanwhile, their investigation of a two-month-long yard sale leads to an armed fugitive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911220000 +0000" stop="20240911223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Dad</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye writes home, describing Christmas in Korea: Radar ships a jeep home, a piece at a time; Henry gives the monthly lecture on sex, with the aid of figure A and figure B; Trapper helps deliver a calf; Klinger and Frank get into a fight, but Father Mulcahy smoothes things over; Hawkeye and Trapper sabotage Margaret's tent; Hawkeye flies to the front line dressed as Santa to help a wounded soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911223000 +0000" stop="20240911230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Edwina</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The nurses go to extreme lengths to find a date for Nurse Eddie—they won't go out with anyone until Eddie gets a date. The men draw straws, and Hawkeye is the big loser, especially after Eddie nearly kills him in a scene resembling teenage "mating" rituals.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911230000 +0000" stop="20240911233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Love Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar gets a Dear John recording from home. Hawkeye and Trapper try to set him up with a date, but fail. Radar is taken by a new nurse at the camp and she is into poetry and music, so they coach him. Margaret wants to stop the relationship, so Hawkeye and Trapper get between her and Frank until she relents. Radar's "Ahhhh, Bach!" and "That's highly significant" quotes win him the girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240911233000 +0000" stop="20240912000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Tuttle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye creates a fake doctor, Captain Jonathan S. Tuttle, to give supplies to the local orphans. Henry wants Tuttle to be officer of the day, so Hawkeye creates a fake personnel file, and all his back pay is given to the orphanage. When General Clayton wants to reward his generosity, Hawkeye is forced to invent a story about Tuttle jumping from a chopper without his parachute!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912000000 +0000" stop="20240912003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney And Thelma Lou, Phfftt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E30</episode-num>
    <desc>After Gomer naively tells Thelma Lou that Barney thinks "he has her in his hip pocket." Thelma Lou decides to teach Barney a lesson by flirting with Gomer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912003000 +0000" stop="20240912010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Back To Nature</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy, Barney and Gomer take a group of boys camping in the mountains to show them the pioneer life. Barney winds up getting himself and Gomer lost in the woods, and it's up to Andy to save the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912010000 +0000" stop="20240912013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Social Climbers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny gets a letter from home, from Adeline Ashley, a hillbilly socialite. Miss Ashley says she going to stop by while visiting friends. However, she arrives early. And through her whole visit, she sets her sights on marrying Jed. Jed isn’t at all interested, but hopes that Miss Ashley could meet Mrs. Drysdale and arranges it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912013000 +0000" stop="20240912020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>The Day Of Decision</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Lisa agreed to try out Green Acres for six months. Today's the day she decides whether to stay in Hooterville or return to New York. Everyone anxiously awaits her decision. In the meantime, Oliver flashes back to their first days on the farm, his physical mishaps around the house, and Haney's lousy products.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912020000 +0000" stop="20240912023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Kommandant Gertrude</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan must get a U.S. general out of Stalag 13, while Klink plans to move the camp's fence line and Gertrude arrives with her fiancé.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912023000 +0000" stop="20240912030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan's Double Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>When Hogan is identified as a saboteur, he impersonates a German officer in front of the very Gestapo agent who could take him down.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912030000 +0000" stop="20240912033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Family Sketch Show</sub-title>
    <desc>"Family Sketch Show. Originally aired on 02/16/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912033000 +0000" stop="20240912043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Tragic Trophy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A Hollywood wheeler-dealer is in desperate need of cash and has gotten himself in some trouble with the ladies. But before things can get any worse, he turns up dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912043500 +0000" stop="20240912050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Kind Of A Stopwatch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is given a stopwatch that allows him to halt time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912050500 +0000" stop="20240912060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Starring The Defense  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When his child is accused of murder, former actor Miles Crawford decides to "act" as the boy's legal representative.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912060500 +0000" stop="20240912070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Blind Mirror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Winifred, private secretary and lover of the publisher George Diamond, becomes a runaway witness when a woman falls into the sea and drowns after a quarrel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912070500 +0000" stop="20240912080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Triangle Of Terror</sub-title>
    <desc>"Kathy Ackers hires Cannon to find out why her father, a banker, committed suicide at a Caribbean resort. She thinks he was murdered, and wants Cannon to prove it. But the man was embezzling from his own bank, so maybe he did have a motive to kill himself..."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912080500 +0000" stop="20240912090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Taste For Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A young man's long-range plans clash with his girlfriend's personal ambition, leading them to commit murder out of greed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912090000 +0000" stop="20240912093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Suspected Cop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Mathews must prove a patrolman's innocence before a newspaper prints the story.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912093000 +0000" stop="20240912100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Hit And Run Driver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon use newspapers, radio and TV to publicize their clues to the identity of a hit-and-run driver.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912100000 +0000" stop="20240912103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Bookie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday goes undercover with the department's chaplain in order to bust a gambling ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912103000 +0000" stop="20240912110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 93 -- Once A Junkie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A former convict and informant who Malloy helped give a second chance is accused of assaulting a priest, dealing drugs and stealing a gun after being fired from his dish-washing job at Duke's Longhorn Café. Malloy and Reed set out to determine if his story, which is full of suspicious coincidences, is actually true.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912110000 +0000" stop="20240912120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Unlikely Duos</sub-title>
    <desc>"In a special 800th episode, extra ordinary best friends Bill and Toony discuss other unconventional pairings, from frenemies to cuisine."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912120000 +0000" stop="20240912123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Sees America</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has the chance to travel around the country for six weeks during the summer and he's all excited about it. However, he quickly realizes when he's gone Gilbert will go after the girl Beaver has a crush on, Mary Margaret. But he quickly realizes, there's more to life than Mary Margaret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912123000 +0000" stop="20240912130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Clothing Drive</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver's school is having a clothing drive and whoever brings in the most clothes will be awarded 1,000 school points. June, Ward and Wally round up all the old clothes they can find and put them in a box. However, next to the box are three good suits of Ward's that are to be cleaned, and, of course, Beaver mistakes them as items for the clothing drive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912130000 +0000" stop="20240912140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Sardonic Sergeant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Major Frank Lessing, a payroll officer on an Army base, is found murdered and Sergeant Joseph Dexter is charged with the crime. The case hinges on a payroll robbery committed in the Philippines years before.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912140000 +0000" stop="20240912150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Blind Justice  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Michelle defends college chum Andrea Morrow after she is accused of murdering her abusive lover, Clay Graham. Matlock soon becomes convinced that the murderer was Clay's blind friend, Arthur Hampton, but has a devil of a time proving how a blind man managed to carry off a near-perfect murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912150000 +0000" stop="20240912160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Triangle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A man murders his wife and her lover after he catches them together, then flees to a remote cabin with his daughter who does not know what he has done. The chief and the boys hope to talk him into surrendering without resorting to violence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912160000 +0000" stop="20240912170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Ferris Wheel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Elizabeth has nightmares about being trapped on a Ferris wheel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912170000 +0000" stop="20240912180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Intruder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Festus is escorting wounded prisoner Riley Sharp to Dodge. They are forced to stop at a farmhouse, where Sharp's ex-wife and her brutish husband live.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912180000 +0000" stop="20240912190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Countess</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Unsettling events that could spell financial ruin for the Ponderosa mysteriously coincide with the arrival of a wealthy countess who seems determined to win the love of Ben Cartwright, the man she spurned 20 years before in New Orleans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912190000 +0000" stop="20240912193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>A Matter Of Faith</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Although a drought has forced local cowhands to seek work on a railroad construction project, railroad executives are afraid that their workers will desert them if they believe an old man's claim that he has found a way to make rain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912193000 +0000" stop="20240912200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Blood Brothers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas McCain gives blood to save a dying man and is surprised by Marshal Torrance's odd behavior toward the man. Then three men arrive from a nearby town and demand custody of the stranger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912200000 +0000" stop="20240912210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Estaban Zamora Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Flint finds a young man bleeding to death and a knife nearby. He takes the body to the sheriff who identifies the man as the youngest Zamora brother. He feels duty-bound to kill the murderer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912210000 +0000" stop="20240912213000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Gifts And Long Letters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed begin today's patrol by investigating a deluded and reclusive parolee whose troubled girlfriend in the apartment next door has just attempted suicide for the second time. In the meantime, they provide vital information to a detective's search for an armed robbery suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912213000 +0000" stop="20240912220000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>O'brien's Stand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy's headstrong and elderly apartment manager stages a protest at the station after she's victimized by a serial purse snatcher, and Malloy suggests a stakeout will be their only chance to apprehend the suspect. On patrol, he and Reed chase a suspicious vehicle into a lumber yard, and investigate the murder of a young man at his parents' home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912220000 +0000" stop="20240912223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Ringbanger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Trapper operate on a famous Colonel - after discovering that he is particularly ruthless about sacrificing his men, they come up with a scheme to get him sent back to the states with a little unwitting help from Frank, Margaret, and a drunk Henry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912223000 +0000" stop="20240912230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Sometimes You Hear The Bullet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank throws his back out while spending the evening with Margaret, and ends up in traction. He promptly applies for the Purple Heart, having been 'technically' wounded at a frontline unit. Tommy Gillis, an old friend of Hawkeye's, is writing a book about the war, and pays him a visit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912230000 +0000" stop="20240912233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Dad, Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Once again, Hawkeye writes home to his father, telling him of the latest gossip: the camp gets a new surgeon, who turns out to be a fake; Hawkeye bets he can walk into the mess tent naked for lunch and no one will notice; and Radar cheats on his final exam.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240912233000 +0000" stop="20240913000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Long-john Flap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp suffers from the severe cold, except for Hawkeye who has received some long johns from his father. They get passed around from person to person as a gift, a gambling stake, a trade, a bribe, stolen and given up to Father Mulcahy, who ends up giving them away.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913000000 +0000" stop="20240913003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer Pyle, U.s.m.c.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer comes to the courthouse one day with an announcement—he has decided to join the Marines, believing it a test of his manhood.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913003000 +0000" stop="20240913010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie Loves Helen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie develops a crush on his teacher, Helen Crump, at the school dance. He spends .74 cents to buy her a gift.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913010000 +0000" stop="20240913013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jethro's Military Career</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro is practicing being a Navy Frogman. Granny, who has been testing her flu serum, a.k.a. moonshine, sees Jethro and thinks there is a monster in the pool. When she tells Jed, he thinks it is a result of her moonshine. But Granny finally is shown that it isn’t a monster, but Jethro. Jed decides that Jethro needs some type of guidance, so he calls Miss Jane, who tells Drysdale.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913013000 +0000" stop="20240913020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>The Engagement Ring</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Eb is sent packing when Darlene's dad learns he proposed to is daughter with a watch fob instead of a ring. Lisa gives Eb the $2000 ring Oliver used to get engaged to her and everyone is happy--until the father has the ring appraised.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913020000 +0000" stop="20240913023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>A Russian Is Coming</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan tries to get a Russian pilot, who refuses to escape to London, back to Russia.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913023000 +0000" stop="20240913030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Rockets Or Romance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan becomes the partner of a beautiful underground agent when he and his men team up with the underground to destroy a guided missile battery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913030000 +0000" stop="20240913033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Pat Carroll And Jack Jones</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Pat Carroll and Jack Jones. Originally aired on 02/23/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913033000 +0000" stop="20240913043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Reckless Rockhound</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When a businessman responsible for decimating a local mining business returns to town, it is not long before he is found murdered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913043500 +0000" stop="20240913050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Night Of A Jockey</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A dejected jockey wants to be tall.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913050500 +0000" stop="20240913060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Cadaver  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A medical undergraduate tries to get his roommate off the bottle by making him believe he killed a young woman while in a drunken trance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913060500 +0000" stop="20240913070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Harlequin's Gold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix searches for Australian sailor Paul Gantry, who is supposedly due to inherit a million dollars.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913070500 +0000" stop="20240913080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Stalker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Reclusive Virginia McKellar insists her sister did not die five years earlier, as everyone believes, and she'll willing to pay Cannon to prove it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913080500 +0000" stop="20240913090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Final Burial</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman hires Barnaby to find her missing husband and the detective's investigation uncovers bigamy, blackmail and murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913090000 +0000" stop="20240913093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Trojan Horse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Mathews works hard to outsmart three desperate criminals who  resort to using a clever ruse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913093000 +0000" stop="20240913100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Subscription Racket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday learns about a scam artist with a novel twist: he uses an authentic Congressional Medal of Honor to solicit magazine subscriptions.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913100000 +0000" stop="20240913103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A Japanese widow is senselessly murdered, leaving her small daughter an orphan. Friday has a hard time controlling his emotions while seeking the killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913103000 +0000" stop="20240913110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 123 -- Courtroom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed feels a strong sense of accomplishment when he stumbles upon a large stash of narcotics as he secures a residence after executing a traffic warrant with Malloy and Officer Ed Wells. He's in for a rude awakening at the trial, however, when he's cross examined by the defense attorney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913110000 +0000" stop="20240913120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Friday The 13th!</sub-title>
    <desc>"On this spooky day, Bill and Toony talk horror, zombies, and more, with the help of a special guest."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913120000 +0000" stop="20240913123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Family Scrapbook</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E39</episode-num>
    <desc>While cleaning, June runs across an old family scrapbook and gathers the family together to reminisce about the past six years. The Cleavers recall scenes from previous episodes including: 'Beaver Gets 'Spelled,'' 'New Neighbors,' 'My Brother's Girl,' 'The Shave,' 'Beaver Runs Away,' 'Larry Hides Out,' 'Teacher Comes to Dinner,' and 'Wally's Election.'</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913123000 +0000" stop="20240913130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Gets "spelled"</sub-title>
    <desc>"Beaver's teacher, Miss Canfield, sends a note home with Beaver and the other kids convince him that it's news that he's getting kicked out of school. So Beaver and Wally take steps to hide the note from Ward and June."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913130000 +0000" stop="20240913140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Curious Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Rhoda Reynolds is charged with murdering her blackmailing ex-husband, Arthur Kane. At the trial, Mason moves the proceedings to the room in which Kane was murdered in order to re-enact the fatal night.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913140000 +0000" stop="20240913150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Annihilator  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>At Cassie's request, Matlock reluctantly agrees to represent a famous wrestler accused of killing a long-time rival. The key witness is a young girl whose story might not be completely accurate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913150000 +0000" stop="20240913160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Hello In There</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Bubba refuses to believe that a former teammate embezzled funds from the bank where he worked. And sets out to prove that his friend was framed and murdered. Harriet hopes that art therapy can help the man's traumatized son, who becomes a target himself when the killer realizes he witnessed the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913160000 +0000" stop="20240913170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Elopement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>The forestry student who previously visited Waltons Mountain (in "The Competition"") now returns</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913170000 +0000" stop="20240913180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Good Samaritans</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt is taking a signed confession paper to a judge that will hang a man. The man has put a reward on the paper causing two bounty hunters to shoot Matt in an effort to get it. Matt is taken in by a group of freed slaves heading west who are being pursued by hunters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913180000 +0000" stop="20240913190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Horse Breaker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>While working at the Ponderosa, wrangler Johnny Lightly suffers an accident that costs him the use of both legs. Though Dr. Kay theorizes that the injuries may not last, Johnny has given up the will to live.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913190000 +0000" stop="20240913193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Stranger At Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark's finding the body of a murder victim starts Lucas, his friend, Artemus, and Marshal Torrance on a search for the killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913193000 +0000" stop="20240913200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Raid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E37</episode-num>
    <desc>When renegade Apaches wound Lucas and kidnap Mark, Marshal Torrance joins with U.S. Marshal Sam Buckhart to form a rescue posse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913200000 +0000" stop="20240913210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Elizabeth Mcqueeny Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Elizabeth McQueeny is traveling with her girls, heading to a finishing school in the west. When her real purpose becomes known, all the females want her gone but her worth shows itself before that can happen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913210000 +0000" stop="20240913213000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Clear With A Civilian: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed starts a flu epidemic that decimates the city's police force, forcing him and Malloy to work a double shift. During day watch, he and Malloy encounter a bookmaker being held at gunpoint, mediate a dispute over a cantaloupe, investigate a possible robbery in progress, engage in a foot chase with an athletic young man and pull over a motorist who turns out to be a VIP.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913213000 +0000" stop="20240913220000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Clear With A Civilian: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Newly appointed Police Commissioner Edna Dixon accompanies Malloy and Reed on night watch, where they deal with a naked elderly wino at a bar, try to diffuse a possible riot situation following a gang-related stabbing and pursue a deaf teenager in a stolen car.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913220000 +0000" stop="20240913223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Army-navy Game</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp tunes into the Army/Navy football game, only to be shelled and have an unexploded bomb land in the middle of the compound. They ring around trying to identify the bomb, and the camp prepares for the worst. Hawkeye and Trapper are left the task of following instructions to disarm the bomb.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913223000 +0000" stop="20240913230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Sticky Wicket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Frank argue over Frank's surgical ability. Hawkeye performs a difficult operation and the patient does not recover as he should. Hawkeye begins to doubt his ability and moves out of The Swamp. He decides to open up his patients again, and discovers a nick in the colon that even Frank admits anyone could have missed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913230000 +0000" stop="20240913233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Major Fred C. Dobbs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank's normal drone of verbal abuse upsets Ginger, so Hawkeye puts his arm in a cast while he is asleep. Frank puts in for a transfer, and after Franks tells Margaret he's leaving, she decides to leave as well. As a result, Col. Blake puts both Hawk and Trap on double post-op duty until he finds replacements for Majs. Burns and Houlihan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240913233000 +0000" stop="20240914000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Cease-fire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>General Clayton calls to say that a ceasefire is to be declared. The camp celebrates, Klinger gives away his dresses and locals start to take pieces of the camp. But Trapper does not believe it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240914000000 +0000" stop="20240914003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's Physical</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney learns that in order to pass the mandatory physical for the deputy's office, he must weigh more and be taller. Andy and Aunt Bee try to stretch him and fatten him up, until Andy comes up with the solution.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240914003000 +0000" stop="20240914010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Family Visit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The Taylors quickly realize why they haven't invited Bee's sister and her husband, Ollie, for a visit in more than a decade. When Uncle Ollie borrows Andy's squad car to go fishing, it's the final straw.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240914010000 +0000" stop="20240914013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Reserve Program</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro is getting ready to enter the reserves, and the Clampetts are giving him a party, with gifts, including lady fingers, a squirrel rifle and a Confederate uniform. Jethro heads down to the reserve where they are preparing to shoot a Civil War movie. The men there think Jethro is an actor for the movie. Jethro soon thinks that the Civil War is going to happen again and rushes home to tell Granny and Elly. Granny decides to take up the fight to make sure the South wins, again, since she is convinced they won the first time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240914013000 +0000" stop="20240914020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>The Deputy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Sam Drucker's off for a two-week vacation to visit his sister, leaving Oliver to take over his duties as deputy sheriff. Complications ensue when Oliver demonstrates how to use a pair of handcuffs to Lisa before discovering that he's lost the keys.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240914020000 +0000" stop="20240914023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Informer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Lieutenant Carter enters the camp and Hogan discovers a spy among his men.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240914023000 +0000" stop="20240914030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hold That Tiger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The POWs smuggle a tiger tank, about which Klink has been boasting, into camp in order to photograph and study it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240914030000 +0000" stop="20240914033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Jane Connell And Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Jane Connell and Tim Conway. Originally aired on 03/02/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240914033000 +0000" stop="20240914043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Latent Lover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A man left unhinged by his wife's affair has been acting out in very strange ways, even attempting to rob a bank in his despair. And when his wife ends up murdered, he is the natural suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240914043500 +0000" stop="20240914050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Old Man In The Cave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A mysterious guardian helps a tiny community survive after nuclear war destroys much of the Earth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240914050500 +0000" stop="20240914060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Dividing Wall  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A break-in gang's newest heist may be their last: the booty contains a radioactive capsule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240914060500 +0000" stop="20240914070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Walk On The Blind Side</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Syndicate thugs have kidnapped an informer—or so they believe. Their victim is actually Peggy Fair, Mannix's secretary, which puts the detective on their trail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240914070500 +0000" stop="20240914080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Kelly's Song</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The man who arranged the death of an embezzler cannot find the loot. But Cannon might, when he investigates on behalf of the man framed for the murder. But Cannon's client might be closer to the case than he lets on.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240914080500 +0000" stop="20240914090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Portrait Of Evil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>An art collector's wife plots to steal one of his paintings, but her plan is complicated by her husband's death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240914090000 +0000" stop="20240914093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Hey, Look Me Over</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Billie Jo becomes jealous of her sweetheart, aviator Steve Elliott, and her youngest sister, Betty Jo.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
